[speaker-01] Eggie.
埃吉。
[speaker-02] Mind if I share your cab?
介意我占用你的车吗？
[speaker-03] Charlie.
查理。
[speaker-04] It's ironic, isn't it?
真是讽刺，不是吗？
[speaker-04] You look like a gentleman.
你看起来像位绅士。
[speaker-04] I look like a pleb.
我看起来像个普通人。
[speaker-04] If I was you, I'd unlock your cab.
如果我是你，我会打开你的车。
[speaker-05] P, get off it!
喂，别说了！
[speaker-06] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-06] Ah!
啊！
[speaker-08] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-05] Ah!
啊！
[speaker-08] Ah.
啊。
[speaker-06] Oh no!
哦，不！
[speaker-08] Whoa!
哇！
[speaker-08] That shit's gonna work this time.
这次这招肯定能奏效。
[speaker-08] You're weighing your death.
你正在权衡自己的死亡。
[speaker-08] Ah!
啊！
[speaker-05] Whoa!
哇！
[speaker-06] Huh.
哼。
[speaker-01] Oh!
哦！
[speaker-08] Ah!
啊！
[speaker-05] We've got a cold purple.
我们拥有一种冰冷的紫色。
[speaker-05] My driver's down.
我的司机倒下了。
[speaker-05] Permission to blow these fuckers.
允许使用这些玩意儿。
[speaker-05] Denied cannot be contained.
不允许包含“Denied”。
[speaker-05] Head south.
向南前进。
[speaker-05] I'm clearing the route.
我正在清理路线。
[speaker-06] Yeah.
是的。
[speaker-05] I'm entering Hyde Park.
我正在进入海德公园。
[speaker-05] Can I get on with it?
我可以继续下去吗？
[speaker-06] Dark zone confirmed.
已确认为黑暗区域。
[speaker-05] Permission to fire.
允许开火。
[speaker-05] The fuck for that.
真他妈讨厌。
[speaker-05] No time to relax.
没有时间休息。
[speaker-05] The police are right behind you.
警察就在你身后。
[speaker-05] You have thirty seconds before they reach your position.
你只有三十秒时间，他们就要到达你的位置了。
[speaker-05] Go directly to rendezvous, Swan.
直接前往集合点吧，斯旺。
[speaker-05] Merlin, you do realise I haven't even got a windscreen right now.
梅林，你难道没意识到我现在连挡风玻璃都没有吗？
[speaker-05] I seem to remember from your training you were rather good at holding y
我记得在训练时你很擅长保持平衡。
[speaker-05] our breath.
我们的呼吸。
[speaker-08] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-05] It wasn't a revenge mission.
这不是一场复仇任务。
[speaker-05] Charlie could have just killed.
查理本可以杀人的。
[speaker-04] Just kill you immediately.
立刻杀了你。
[speaker-05] No.
不。
[speaker-02] No boasting, Bob.
不要自夸，鲍勃。
[speaker-05] I trained him well enough that even he wouldn't mess that up.
我训练得足够好，就连他也不会搞砸。
[speaker-05] Merlin, I'm sorry.
梅林，对不起。
[speaker-05] We're going to have to do the debrief tomorrow.
明天我们不得不进行总结汇报。
[speaker-05] I've got to get to a dinner tonight, and if I miss it,
我今晚必须去吃晚餐，如果错过就来不及了。
[speaker-05] let's just say Charlie might as well.
我们就说，查理本可以这么做吧。
[speaker-05] if you can't wait for the police to clear the park.
如果你不能等待警察清理公园的话。
[speaker-02] There's another way out.
还有另一种出路。
[speaker-05] in the corner.
在角落里。
[speaker-05] How important is that dinner?
那顿晚餐有多重要？
[speaker-02] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-05] Let me show you.
让我来展示给你看。
[speaker-08] I'm going to go in there and get it.
我打算去那里把它拿回来。
[speaker-08] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-08] I'm not sure what's going on.
我不确定发生了什么。
[speaker-08] I'm going to have to go.
我得去一下。
[speaker-08] I'm gonna take you to the edge.
我打算带你去到边缘处。
[speaker-08] I'm not sure.
我不确定。
[speaker-08] I'm sorry.
对不起。
[speaker-06] For fuck's sake.
看在老天的份上。
[speaker-05] Babe.
宝贝。
[speaker-05] I'm home.
我在家。
[speaker-05] I'm here.
我在这里。
[speaker-05] What the hell happened?
到底发生了什么？
[speaker-05] It's a long story that deserves a kiss.
这是个很长的故事，值得一个吻。
[speaker-05] Not even J.
甚至不需要 J。
[speaker-05] would kiss you right now.
现在就吻你。
[speaker-05] If you really love me, just one little kiss.
如果你真的爱我，就一个小小的吻吧。
[speaker-02] Ah.
啊。
[speaker-05] You were really gonna do it?
你真的打算这么做吗？
[speaker-05] Now that is true love, right there.
这真就是真爱，没错。
[speaker-05] I'm gonna go get changed.
我打算去换衣服。
[speaker-08] Yeah.
是的。
[speaker-05] Happy birthday to you.
祝你生日快乐。
[speaker-05] Woo!
哇！
[speaker-05] Hey!
嘿！
[speaker-05] Tildy made that for you herself, bro.
Tildy是自己为你做的，兄弟。
[speaker-05] Yeah, what?
是的，什么？
[speaker-05] The royal baker's not available.
皇家面包师无法使用。
[speaker-02] Shut up, Brandon.
闭嘴，布兰登。
[speaker-05] Especially if you want some of this.
尤其是如果你想要一些这些的话。
[speaker-05] Is that Swedish stuff?
那是瑞典语的内容吗？
[speaker-05] Like, no, I ain't drinking under that.
喜欢，不，我可不会在那儿喝酒。
[speaker-05] Last time.
上次。
[speaker-05] yeah, I was wrecked, man.
是的，我彻底崩溃了，兄弟。
[speaker-05] Yeah, but that's 'cause you're a lightweight, Jamal.
是的，但那是因为你很轻松，贾马尔。
[speaker-05] No, babe, I'm good.
不，亲爱的，我没事。
[speaker-05] Not for me, thank you.
不，谢谢。
[speaker-05] What's going on, man?
怎么了，兄弟？
[speaker-05] I'll meet her parents for the first time tomorrow night.
明天晚上我将第一次见到她的父母。
[speaker-05] I wanna make a good impression.
我想留下好印象。
[speaker-05] Oh, yeah, Jamal.
哦，对，贾马尔。
[speaker-05] By the way, you free to dog sit JB tomorrow night while we're there?
顺便问一下，我们明天晚上在那里的时候，你明天晚上可以帮忙照顾JB的狗吗？
[speaker-05] Ah, sorry, bruv.
啊，抱歉，兄弟。
[speaker-05] I gotta look after my nan tomorrow.
明天我得照顾我的奶奶。
[speaker-05] But Liam's free, though.
不过利亚姆有空。
[speaker-05] Oh, yeah.
哦，对。
[speaker-05] I can't, mate.
不行，兄弟。
[speaker-05] I'm allergic to dogs.
我对狗过敏。
[speaker-05] Bullshits.
胡说八道。
[speaker-05] Dog shit, actually.
狗屎，实际上。
[speaker-01] That.
那个。
[speaker-05] leaves you, Brandon.
留给你，布兰登。
[speaker-05] What are you doing tomorrow night?
明天晚上你在做什么？
[speaker-05] Yeah, I'll look after your dog, mate.
是的，我会照顾你的狗，兄弟。
[speaker-05] But I've got one condition.
但我有一个条件。
[speaker-05] Sir, you have a drink with us.
先生，您可以与我们一起喝一杯。
[speaker-05] Yeah, come on, baby.
是的，来吧，宝贝。
[speaker-01] Brandon, happy birthday!
布兰登，生日快乐！
[speaker-05] Happy birthday!
生日快乐！
[speaker-05] Cheers!
干杯！
[speaker-05] Woo!
哇！
[speaker-08] Yeah.
是的。
[speaker-05] My drugs are everywhere.
我的药片到处都是。
[speaker-05] They were never my thing,
它们从来不是我的喜好。
[speaker-05] but here I am running the biggest drug cartel in the world.
但如今我却掌控着世界上最大的毒品贩毒集团。
[speaker-05] The only downside is having to live in the middle of nowhere.
唯一的缺点就是不得不住在偏僻的地方。
[speaker-05] You know, these ruins are technically undiscovered.
你知道，从技术上讲，这些废墟还未被发现。
[speaker-05] I just added a few touches to remind me of home.
我只是加了几处细节，以让我想起家乡。
[speaker-05] I grew upon all that awesome fiftys nostalgia.
在那种令人惊叹的五十年代怀旧氛围中，我逐渐成长起来。
[speaker-05] Grease, American graffiti, happy days.
油脂、美国涂鸦、快乐的时光。
[speaker-05] But I digress.
不过我偏离主题了。
[speaker-05] The thing you need to understand.
你需要理解的那件事。
[speaker-05] Is the hard work and ingenuity it took to achieve a global monopoly?
实现全球垄断所付出的辛勤劳动和智慧是否必要？
[speaker-05] On the drug trade.
在毒品交易上。
[speaker-05] And that's all on me—not to toot my own horn.
这就是全部了——不是为了自夸。
[speaker-05] I just think it's really important for new recruits to understand.
我认为新兵们理解这一点非常重要。
[speaker-05] The history of the golden circle.
金环的历史。
[speaker-05] So, lifelong friends, huh?
那么，终身好友呢？
[speaker-05] Charles, you think your buddy here's worthy of joining us?
查尔斯，你认为你的朋友值得加入我们吗？
[speaker-08] Miss Poppy, I would not have.
波比小姐，我不会那样做。
[speaker-03] I'd have brought him all the way to see if I didn't think so.
我本打算带他过来看看，如果我没这么想的话。
[speaker-05] Well, you hungry?
嗯，你饿了吗？
[speaker-05] Starving.
渴望。
[speaker-03] Wonderful.
很好。
[speaker-05] Right this way.
往这边走。
[speaker-05] Make yourselves at home.
请随意相处。
[speaker-05] So, fellas.
那么，伙计们。
[speaker-05] I have a couple of things that I want to clarify.
我有几件事想要说明清楚。
[speaker-05] You understand that in the golden circle,
你明白在金色圈中，
[speaker-05] my authority is never to be questioned.
我的权威绝不容置疑。
[speaker-05] Right, and the importance of following orders—you understand that.
对了，遵守命令的重要性——你明白的。
[speaker-05] The value of loyalty.
忠诚的价值。
[speaker-05] It's easy to nod, isn't it?
点头很容易，对吧？
[speaker-05] I don't like easy.
我不喜欢简单的事情。
[speaker-05] I like proof.
我喜欢证据。
[speaker-05] What's your name?
您叫什么名字？
[speaker-02] Mom.
妈妈。
[speaker-05] Angel, baby, hey.
天使，宝贝，嘿。
[speaker-08] Your old pouch.
你的旧口袋。
[speaker-05] Charles has messed up.
查尔斯搞砸了。
[speaker-05] That's all I'm gonna tell you, 'cause that's all you need to know.
这就是我要告诉你的全部内容，因为这就是你需要知道的全部。
[speaker-05] So put him in the mincer, okay?
所以把他放进绞肉机里吧，好吗？
[speaker-05] Haha.
哈哈。
[speaker-02] Ha!
哈！
[speaker-05] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-02] Hahaha!
哈哈哈哈！
[speaker-08] Mmm.
嗯。
[speaker-05] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-08] Okay.
[speaker-08] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-08] I'm sorry.
对不起。
[speaker-08] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-08] I'm going to go to the bathroom.
我要去洗手间。
[speaker-08] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-05] Oh.
[speaker-08] Oh!
哦！
[speaker-08] Now, let me smell it, dog!
现在，让我闻一闻，狗！
[speaker-06] Ah!
啊！
[speaker-08] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-08] Oh!
哦！
[speaker-06] Good job.
干得好。
[speaker-05] See my salon across the way.
请看看我隔条街的那家沙龙。
[speaker-05] Head there for your makeover.
去那边接受造型设计吧。
[speaker-08] Aegy, I hope you're hungry.
哎呀，希望你们饿了。
[speaker-05] Oh, babe.
哦，宝贝。
[speaker-02] I was gonna grab breakfast.
我本来打算去吃早餐。
[speaker-05] Just at work.
就在工作期间。
[speaker-05] This looks lovely, but I'm running late.
这看起来很漂亮，但我迟到了。
[speaker-05] I just thought maybe we could practice.
我刚想，也许我们可以练习一下。
[speaker-05] For tonight, practice.
今晚就练习吧。
[speaker-05] Eating.
进食。
[speaker-05] You said you'd never eaten at a palace before.
你之前说从未在宫殿里吃过饭。
[speaker-05] Papa is sort of picky about table manners.
爸爸对餐桌礼仪有点挑剔。
[speaker-05] Well, as it happens, babe.
嗯，巧的是，亲爱的。
[speaker-02] I've got this shit on lock.
我已经完全掌握了这个内容。
[speaker-05] I know what every single one of them knives and forks is for.
我知道每把刀和每把叉子是用来做什么的。
[speaker-02] This is a butter knife.
这是一把黄油刀。
[speaker-04] the only one you need to remember.
只需记住这一个。
[speaker-04] The rest of the cutlery is easy.
剩下的餐具就简单了。
[speaker-04] You start from the outside and you work your way in with each course.
你从外部开始，逐步深入每个环节。
[speaker-04] And never let anyone describe you as H K L P.
永远不要让任何人称你为 H K L P。
[speaker-04] What's that?
那是什么？
[speaker-04] Holds knife like pen,
像笔一样握持刀子，
[speaker-04] a habit erroneously believed to be upper-class dining etiquette.
一种被错误地认为属于上层社会餐饮礼仪的习惯。
[speaker-04] It is quite the opposite.
恰恰相反。
[speaker-04] White wine, pudding wine, red wine, water, and pop.
白葡萄酒、布丁酒、红葡萄酒、水和啤酒。
[speaker-04] Or whatever, Tipple takes your fancy.
或者随便什么，只要符合你的喜好即可。
[speaker-04] Am I supposed to wait for everyone else to be served before I start eati
我应该等其他人都上菜后才能开始吃吗？
[speaker-05] Only if the dish.
仅当该菜肴如此时。
[speaker-04] being served is cold, or if the queen is present.
正在上菜时很冷，或者如果女王在场的话。
[speaker-04] Otherwise, tuck in.
否则，就开始吃吧。
[speaker-05] Gotta be honest, never really thought the royalty bit.
说实话，我从未真正考虑过皇室相关的内容。
[speaker-04] It'd be relevant.
这很相关。
[speaker-05] Harry would have been chuffed.
哈里会很高兴的。
[speaker-05] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-05] I wish I could have met him.
真希望我能遇见他。
[speaker-05] You miss him too, don't you, Mr.
你也很想念他，对吧，先生？
[speaker-05] Pickle?
泡菜？
[speaker-05] Hmm.
嗯。
[speaker-05] Pickle says, "Yeah.
泡菜说：“是的。”
[speaker-05] Sit down.
坐下来。
[speaker-05] I'm fine.
我很好。
[speaker-05] Have a good day.
祝你有美好的一天。
[speaker-05] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-02] Got a hat.
得到一顶帽子。
[speaker-02] You're late.
你迟到了。
[speaker-02] We were wondering if you'd had a second encounter with Charlie.
我们想知道你是否再次与查理见面了。
[speaker-05] I'm looking forward to finishing him off.
我期待着彻底解决他。
[speaker-05] All right, gents.
好的，各位。
[speaker-02] Marlin, come in.
马林，进来吧。
[speaker-02] Galahad and Launcelot, please remain for Merlin's debrief.
加拉哈德和兰斯洛特，请留在这里等待马林的汇报。
[speaker-02] Everyone else, reconvene at nineteen hundred hours.
其他所有人，在十九点零分时再次集合。
[speaker-05] So.
所以。
[speaker-02] The man who attacked Galahad in the taxi was Charlie Hesketh.
在出租车上袭击加拉哈德的那个人是查理·赫斯凯斯。
[speaker-02] Rejected Kingsman applicant turned bad.
被拒的金士曼候选人变得糟糕了。
[speaker-02] We last saw him back at Richmond Valentine's HQ.
我们上次是在里士满瓦伦丁总部见到他的。
[speaker-02] Like everyone else there, Charlie had a security implant in his neck.
和其余人一样，查理的脖子上植入了安全植入物。
[speaker-02] A weakness we had no choice but to exploit.
我们不得不利用的一个弱点。
[speaker-05] Hey, man!
嘿，兄弟！
[speaker-05] Still fucking spectacular, eh?
还是那么棒，对吧？
[speaker-05] Come on, guys!
来吧，大家！
[speaker-05] Loosen up.
放松点。
[speaker-05] We saved the world.
我们拯救了世界。
[speaker-02] Yeah, unfortunately, Galahad.
是啊，可惜的是，加拉哈德。
[speaker-02] You also saved Charlie.
你也救了查理。
[speaker-02] When you electrocuted him, you damaged his implant.
当你给他通电时，你损坏了他的植入物。
[speaker-02] Instead of his head exploding, he only lost an arm and his vocal cords.
他不是头部爆炸，只是失去了一条手臂和声带。
[speaker-05] I should be thanking me.
我应该感谢自己。
[speaker-05] And now he's back for revenge.
现在他又回来了，想要复仇。
[speaker-05] We don't think so, sir.
我们不这么认为，先生。
[speaker-02] We believe he's been recruited by an unknown organization.
我们认为他已被某个未知组织招募了。
[speaker-02] That's a lot.
那真多。
[speaker-05] Got the police autopsy reports from Charlie's colleagues in the SUVs.
从查理的 SUV 同事那里得到了警方尸检报告。
[speaker-05] They're not just goons for hire.
他们不仅仅是雇佣的打手。
[speaker-05] Fingerprints removed, teeth filed smooth.
指纹已被清除，牙齿也被打磨得光滑。
[speaker-05] I did a face recognition.
我进行了面部识别。
[speaker-05] Nothing.
无。
[speaker-04] Because.
因为。
[speaker-05] A cosmetic tattoo made of twenty-four karat gold.
由24克拉黄金制成的美容纹身。
[speaker-05] They all had them.
他们全都拥有它们。
[speaker-05] Seems like we're looking at some kind of underworld organisation.
看起来我们面对的是某种黑社会组织。
[speaker-02] Signora Poppy has sent me for my makeover.
波比夫人让我去做造型。
[speaker-02] Follow me.
请跟我来。
[speaker-05] Please take your shirt off.
请脱下你的衬衫。
[speaker-08] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-06] Oh!
哦！
[speaker-08] Ah.
啊。
[speaker-08] Go.
去吧。
[speaker-06] It's beautiful.
真美。
[speaker-05] Isn't it?
不是吗？
[speaker-05] Not that.
不是那样。
[speaker-05] This.
这个。
[speaker-05] Bon appetit.
请尝尝。
[speaker-05] To spoil you.
为了取笑你。
[speaker-05] But it's raining.
但正在下雨。
[speaker-05] Rains in my heart.
心中下着雨。
[speaker-05] What's gonna become?
将会变成什么？
[speaker-05] Maybe.
也许。
[speaker-05] How is it?
怎么样？
[speaker-05] It's delicious.
真美味。
[speaker-02] Issues.
问题。
[speaker-05] Welcome to the golden circle.
欢迎来到金色圈。
[speaker-05] Bring my heart.
带我走吧。
[speaker-04] The hair is yet to grow.
头发还未来得及长成。
[speaker-05] I think.
我认为。
[speaker-04] we should do you the favor.
我们应该帮您一个忙。
[speaker-02] of conversing in English.
以英语进行交流。
[speaker-02] Yes.
是的。
[speaker-04] So, tell me.
那么，请告诉我。
[speaker-02] What do you do?
您做什么工作？
[speaker-02] I work for Kingsman, the tailors.
我在 Kingsman 工作，那里是制衣厂。
[speaker-02] Your Highness, you may address my daughter as your Highness.
殿下，您可以称呼我的女儿为殿下。
[speaker-02] Please address the queen and myself with your majesty, Papa.
请以“陛下”称呼女王和我，爸爸。
[speaker-05] This is a family dinner, not some state function.
这是家庭聚餐，而非官方活动。
[speaker-04] Well then, Eggsy.
那么，埃格斯。
[speaker-02] What do you make of the current situation in the Indian financial market
你对印度金融市场的当前局势有何看法？
[speaker-02] s?
什么？
[speaker-05] Papa.
爸爸。
[speaker-05] Uh.
嗯。
[speaker-05] Well.
那么。
[speaker-02] I don't think we can underestimate the impact of the ECB's.
我认为我们不能低估欧洲央行的影响。
[speaker-04] Quantitative easing.
量化宽松。
[speaker-05] Measures, and of course, the liquidity.
措施，当然还有流动性。
[speaker-02] wave from the.
来自……的波动。
[speaker-05] Federal Reserve rate hike getting pushed back.
联邦储备银行的利率上调被推迟了。
[speaker-02] Frida Kahlo.
弗丽达·卡洛。
[speaker-02] Well.
嗯。
[speaker-05] Other than the one thousand,
除了那一千之外，
[speaker-05] nine hundred and thirty-nine acquisition by the Louvre, she wasn't.
九百三十九件作品被卢浮宫收购，但她没有参与。
[speaker-02] really acknowledged until the new.
直到新时期，这一观点才得到认可。
[speaker-05] The neo-Mexican isekai art movement of the late nineteen seventys.
二十世纪七十年代末的新墨西哥异世界艺术运动。
[speaker-02] Moorish revival.
摩洛哥复兴。
[speaker-02] Ah, the Palazzo Samma.
啊，萨玛宫。
[speaker-05] Sametzano in Tuscany.
托斯卡纳的萨梅茨亚诺。
[speaker-05] Beautiful.
很美。
[speaker-02] Bluetooth technology, which of course.
蓝牙技术，当然了。
[speaker-05] Got its name from the legendary Danish king Harold Blotand.
其名称源自传奇丹麦国王哈罗尔·布洛坦德。
[speaker-05] Whose name translates to Bluetooth.
“蓝牙”这个词的翻译者是谁？
[speaker-05] In English,
用英语来说，
[speaker-05] and the Bluetooth logo is his initials in Norse runic symbols.
蓝牙标志其实是他在北欧符文符号中的名字首字母。
[speaker-05] As I'm sure you know, the Bluetooth logo is his initials.
正如您所知，蓝牙标志其实是他名字的首字母。
[speaker-05] In Norse runic symbols.
在北欧符文符号中。
[speaker-05] My God, Iggy, why isn't he eating his fucking pudding?
天啊，伊吉，为什么他不吃他的布丁呢？
[speaker-05] I need to research this gold tattoo.
我需要研究这个金色纹身。
[speaker-05] I found records of other people with the same body modifications.
我发现了其他人有相同身体改造的记录。
[speaker-05] All of them have high-level involvement with crime and international dru
他们所有人都深度参与犯罪与国际毒品相关事务。
[speaker-05] g trafficking.
g 贩运。
[speaker-05] And there's rumors of something called the golden circle.
还有关于名为“金色圆圈”的传言。
[speaker-04] Hmm.
嗯。
[speaker-05] Best agent or best friend?
最好的助手还是最好的朋友？
[speaker-02] Woof!
汪！
[speaker-05] Come on, Chayve, give it a rest, mate.
来吧，Chayve，冷静点，朋友。
[speaker-08] Stop scratching the door.
不要抓挠门了。
[speaker-03] I'm gonna get to blame that.
那我就要负责了。
[speaker-02] Hey, y'all.
嘿，大家。
[speaker-03] Happy.
高兴。
[speaker-03] Packs and all that.
包装之类的东西。
[speaker-03] Shit, boy!
靠，兄弟！
[speaker-04] You reckon, JB?
你觉得呢，JB？
[speaker-03] Model material.
模型材料。
[speaker-02] Really not as I expected.
真的没有我预期的那么好。
[speaker-02] Thank you very much, Your Majesty.
非常感谢您，陛下。
[speaker-02] Dixie, is that you, mate?
迪克西，是你吗，兄弟？
[speaker-02] What the fuck is going on here?
这到底怎么回事？
[speaker-02] You a gangster now, or something?
你现在成了黑帮分子了吗？
[speaker-02] I was at Tilly's mum and dad's house.
我曾在蒂莉的父母家度过一段时光。
[speaker-03] Tell you what.
告诉你吧。
[speaker-03] Whatever you're doing, I want in.
无论你在做什么，我都要加入进来。
[speaker-02] Put it down.
放下它。
[speaker-02] What this?
这是什么？
[speaker-03] I said.
我说了。
[speaker-02] Put it down now.
现在就放下它。
[speaker-02] What's wrong with it?
怎么了？
[speaker-02] Shut it!
关上它！
[speaker-02] Fucking shut it!
该死！
[speaker-05] I beg your pardon.
请原谅。
[speaker-02] Shut it now!
现在就关上它！
[speaker-02] All right, mate.
好的，伙计。
[speaker-02] Show your best.
展示你的最佳表现。
[speaker-03] We both.
我们俩。
[speaker-02] Eggsy.
[speaker-03] Oh my God!
哦，天哪！
[speaker-03] No, I'm so sorry.
不，非常抱歉。
[speaker-02] You shut up and.
你闭嘴吧。
[speaker-03] I know he got me in enough trouble.
我知道他给我带来了足够的麻烦。
[speaker-08] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-08] Huh.
哼。
[speaker-06] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-03] For the next order of business, Agent Cassel.
接下来要处理的事项，卡塞尔Agent。
[speaker-06] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-08] Oh.
[speaker-06] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-04] I'm sorry.
对不起。
[speaker-08] Oh, fuck.
哦，该死。
[speaker-06] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-08] Oh.
[speaker-02] Yep.
是的。
[speaker-02] Kingsman is grumpy.
金斯曼很生气。
[speaker-03] Bumpets.
高筒靴。
[speaker-05] Like toast.
就像吐司一样。
[speaker-08] But Britain.
但是英国。
[speaker-05] British.
英国的。
[speaker-08] And to say thank.
还有感谢的话。
[speaker-05] you.
你。
[speaker-02] I got you a present, Charlie.
查理，我送你一份礼物。
[speaker-02] My guys made you.
我的朋友们为你准备了礼物。
[speaker-02] This.
这个。
[speaker-02] Bigger, badder, better.
更大、更差、更好。
[speaker-02] I call it arm.
我称之为手臂。
[speaker-02] Again.
再次。
[speaker-08] Huh.
嗯。
[speaker-08] I'm not a man.
我不是男人。
[speaker-08] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-08] I'm going to take a look at the back of the box.
我打算看看盒子的背面。
[speaker-08] I'm going to take a look at the back of the car.
我打算看看汽车的背面。
[speaker-08] Where?
在哪里？
[speaker-06] I'm not a bad person.
我不是个坏人。
[speaker-08] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-02] Let's see if your game improves.
让我们看看你的游戏是否有所改进。
[speaker-08] I'm not sure.
我不确定。
[speaker-08] Woo!
哇！
[speaker-04] Someone decides to wipe.
有人决定清理掉。
[speaker-03] Every Kingsman.
每个《国王曼恩》。
[speaker-05] property.
属性。
[speaker-02] Every agent, and somehow.
每个代理，不知为何。
[speaker-03] Conveniently.
很方便。
[speaker-02] You won at home.
你在家里赢了。
[speaker-03] I could say the same thing about.
关于它，我也可以说同样的话。
[speaker-04] Thinking about you.
想着你。
[speaker-03] What do you think?
你觉得如何？
[speaker-02] See.
见。
[speaker-03] And my mate Brandon, and my fucking dog.
我的伙伴布兰登，还有我的狗。
[speaker-03] No.
不。
[speaker-04] You think I would?
你觉得我会吗？
[speaker-03] This thing.
这个东西。
[speaker-04] Hacked us.
被黑客攻击了。
[speaker-03] Clearly, this arm can be remotely controlled.
显然，这只手臂可以通过远程控制。
[speaker-03] I'm only alive 'cause my address wasn't on the database with the agents.
我之所以还活着，只是因为我的地址没有被代理程序记录在数据库中。
[speaker-03] Whoever Charlie's working with doesn't think that mere staff.
与查理合作的任何人都不会认为只是普通员工而已。
[speaker-03] Are missile worthy.
导弹值得吗？
[speaker-02] This ain't funny.
这一点都不好笑。
[speaker-02] Roxy is dead.
罗克西已经死了。
[speaker-02] Everyone's dead.
所有人都死了。
[speaker-02] Do you even?
你真的吗？
[speaker-03] I don't even care.
我根本不关心。
[speaker-02] Pull yourself together.
冷静一下吧。
[speaker-03] Remember your training.
记住你的训练内容。
[speaker-03] There's no time for emotion in this scenario.
在这种情况下没有时间表达情感。
[speaker-03] Now, as all surviving agents are present.
现在，所有幸存的智能体都到齐了。
[speaker-03] We follow the doomsday protocol.
我们遵循末日协议。
[speaker-03] When that's done.
等那件事办完之后。
[speaker-03] And only then.
只有那样才行。
[speaker-03] You may share the tear in private.
你可以私下分享那滴眼泪。
[speaker-04] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-03] What's the doomsday protocol?
末日协议是什么？
[speaker-02] We go shopping.
我们去购物。
[speaker-03] We're from Kingsman.
我们来自Kingsman。
[speaker-03] We'd like to buy some wine.
我们想买一些葡萄酒。
[speaker-03] And use tasting room number three, please.
请使用第三品鉴室。
[speaker-03] Not one of my predecessors has ever been in this situation before.
我的前任们中从未有人过过这种状况。
[speaker-03] Thank God.
谢天谢地。
[speaker-03] Uh huh.
嗯。
[speaker-03] Remember this?
还记得这个吗？
[speaker-03] How could I?
我该如何做呢？
[speaker-02] I'm not gonna forget.
我不会忘记的。
[speaker-08] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-03] Whatever's in that safe is the answer to all our problems.
那个保险箱里的任何东西都是我们所有问题的答案。
[speaker-08] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-03] Huh.
嗯。
[speaker-08] I'm sorry.
对不起。
[speaker-02] Is that it?
就是那样吗？
[speaker-02] I suppose that must.
我想那一定是如此。
[speaker-03] be upper-class humour.
上流社会的幽默。
[speaker-03] I don't get it.
我不明白。
[speaker-03] What the fuck are we supposed to do now?
我们现在到底该做什么啊？
[speaker-02] I think we should drink.
我觉得我们应该喝点东西。
[speaker-03] To drink a toast to our fallen comrades.
为我们的逝去战友干杯。
[speaker-03] To Roxy.
给罗克西。
[speaker-04] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-03] To Arthur.
给亚瑟。
[speaker-02] Arthur.
亚瑟。
[speaker-02] Mmm.
嗯。
[speaker-02] Should we do one for J B?
我们应该为J B也干一杯吗？
[speaker-02] I think we should.
我认为我们应该如此。
[speaker-03] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-02] Haha.
哈哈。
[speaker-02] I'm sorry.
对不起。
[speaker-03] Should've seen it coming.
应该预料到这一点。
[speaker-02] Charlie, the taxi.
查理，出租车。
[speaker-02] It's all my fault.
都是我的错。
[speaker-02] No, that's bullshit, Merlin!
不，那是胡说，梅林！
[speaker-02] It ain't all your fault.
不是全部都是你的错。
[speaker-02] You're the best, bro.
你太棒了，兄弟。
[speaker-02] Honestly, without you, I'd have.
说实话，没有你，我就会那样做了。
[speaker-02] And I lost it a long time ago.
很久以前我就把它弄丢了。
[speaker-03] I think we should drink to Scotland.
我觉得我们应该为苏格兰干杯。
[speaker-03] I think we.
我觉得我们。
[speaker-02] We've probably had enough, to be honest.
说实话，我们可能已经受够了。
[speaker-03] You're probably right.
你说得对。
[speaker-06] I'm not sure.
我不确定。
[speaker-04] Marlon.
马伦。
[speaker-04] Bye.
再见。
[speaker-03] I think we're going.
我觉得我们正在出发。
[speaker-02] A Kentucky fried chicken.
一只肯塔基炸鸡。
[speaker-03] Hello, fried chicken.
你好，炸鸡。
[speaker-03] Nah, proper campfire.
不，应该是真正的营火。
[speaker-02] Look.
看。
[speaker-03] You know what else, Alum?
你知道还有什么吗，学生？
[speaker-03] Country and western music.
西部国家音乐。
[speaker-03] Country road.
乡村道路。
[speaker-03] Take me home.
带我回家。
[speaker-03] To the place.
到那个地方。
[speaker-03] I belong.
我属于这里。
[speaker-06] I'm not a bad person.
我不是个坏人。
[speaker-08] I'm not afraid to die.
我不怕死。
[speaker-08] Truth be told, folks, we just like the name.
说实话，我们只是喜欢这个名字。
[speaker-08] Here's where we leave the cast.
这就是我们离开剧组的地点。
[speaker-05] Age and.
年龄和。
[speaker-08] Unfortunately, we can't go in.
很遗憾，我们无法进入。
[speaker-05] Is it the temperature control?
是温度控制吗？
[speaker-02] Biometric security scanner,
生物识别安全扫描仪
[speaker-02] just to protect a few old barrels of whiskey.
只是为了保护几桶老威士忌。
[speaker-02] Pull the other one off.
把另一个拿开。
[speaker-03] Got it.
明白。
[speaker-02] You getting anything?
你得到什么了吗？
[speaker-03] Not yet.
尚未。
[speaker-02] Fuck, you know.
该死，你知道的。
[speaker-03] It's not scotch.
这不是苏格兰威士忌。
[speaker-03] Hang on.
等一下。
[speaker-03] According to this,
根据这一点，
[speaker-03] there's a huge underground structure right beneath us.
在我们下方有一个巨大的地下结构。
[speaker-03] And if my calculations are correct.
如果我的计算正确的话。
[speaker-03] This.
这个。
[speaker-03] Is the way in.
是进入的路吗？
[speaker-08] Fucking hell, man!
该死，兄弟！
[speaker-08] You know my mama.
你了解我的妈妈。
[speaker-02] She always told me.
她总是这样告诉我。
[speaker-02] Us Southerners get our good manners from the British.
我们南方人从英国人那里继承了良好的礼仪。
[speaker-02] I was thinking.
我在思考。
[speaker-02] Ain't that a pity?
真遗憾，不是吗？
[speaker-02] Y'all ain't keepin' nothing for yourself.
你们根本没为自己保留任何东西。
[speaker-02] Y'all ain't never heard of knock 'em, vote you in 'em.
你们根本没听说过“投票支持他们”这种说法。
[speaker-02] Well, actually, we had an invitation, didn't we?
嗯，实际上，我们有邀请函，对吧？
[speaker-02] Yeah, how did you know?
是的，你是怎么知道的？
[speaker-02] Yeah, it came in the shape of a bottle.
是的，它呈瓶子形状。
[speaker-02] We're from the Kingsmen Tailors shop in London.
我们来自伦敦的Kingsmen Tailors商店。
[speaker-02] Maybe you've heard of us.
也许你们听说过我们。
[speaker-02] Oh, the Kingsmen.
哦，那些国王们。
[speaker-03] Yeah.
是的。
[speaker-03] Huh.
嗯。
[speaker-02] That's where y'all got them fine suits and them fancy spectacles y'all g
你们那里有那些漂亮的西装和昂贵的眼镜吧？
[speaker-04] That's right.
没错。
[speaker-04] Y'all look damn sharp.
你们看起来真厉害。
[speaker-02] Yard.
码。
[speaker-02] Let me see if I got it right here.
让我看看这里翻译是否正确。
[speaker-02] You want me to believe that it's normal for a tailor?
你希望我相信裁缝工作很正常吗？
[speaker-02] To hack through an advanced biometric security system with nothing but a
仅用工具来突破高级生物识别安全系统……
[speaker-02] A little bitty old watch on.
一只小小的旧手表戴在身上。
[speaker-08] I'm not sure.
我不太确定。
[speaker-02] I can promise you.
我可以向你保证。
[speaker-02] That dog don't hunt.
那只狗不会捕猎。
[speaker-02] want you go on and get down on your knees and tell me who you really wor
请继续跪下来说出你真正的目标是什么。
[speaker-02] k for.
k 用于。
[speaker-08] I'm not sure if I can do this.
我不确定自己能否做到这一点。
[speaker-08] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-02] That's 1963.
那是1963年。
[speaker-02] Statesman Reserve.
政治家储备。
[speaker-02] You just made it personal.
你刚刚变得很私人化了。
[speaker-08] Ah!
啊！
[speaker-08] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-06] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-08] Agh!
啊！
[speaker-08] Ah!
[speaker-08] Gah!
啊！
[speaker-08] I'm not a bad person.
我不是个坏人。
[speaker-04] Who the fuck are you?
你到底是谁？
[speaker-02] A bottle in a secret vault.
一个藏在秘密金库里的瓶子。
[speaker-02] You really expect me to take that seriously?
你真的认为我会把那当回事吗？
[speaker-02] See, I think your story's horseshit.
看吧，我觉得你的故事太荒谬了。
[speaker-02] Y'all just trying to cover for a failed rescue mission.
你们只是在为一次失败的救援任务找借口罢了。
[speaker-02] You here for the leopard dress, ain't she?
你来这里是为了那件豹纹连衣裙，对吧？
[speaker-02] Okay, so your mystery bottle, huh?
好的，那么那个神秘的瓶子呢？
[speaker-02] Look, anything like that, right there?
看吧，就是这样的东西，对吧？
[speaker-02] Yes, same brand.
是的，同一品牌。
[speaker-05] A brand much older.
一个更古老的品牌。
[speaker-02] All right.
好的。
[speaker-02] We'll see here.
我们稍后会看到。
[speaker-02] You know why the measurement of alcohol contents called proof?
你知道为什么酒精含量测量单位叫“proof”吗？
[speaker-05] Oh, fuck off!
哦，去你的！
[speaker-03] For peace' sake.
为了和平起见。
[speaker-02] it comes from back in the old days when pirates—they wanted to test the
它源自过去，当时海盗们——他们想要测试……
[speaker-02] strength of their rum.
他们朗姆酒的酒精度。
[speaker-02] They just pour a little bit out on gunpowder.
他们只是把少量液体倒入火药中。
[speaker-02] That'll make you want to slap your mama right there, boy.
那会让你立刻想揍你妈妈一拳，小子。
[speaker-06] And if you come.
如果你来的话。
[speaker-02] Gunpowder—if it burnt when they set it alight—they consider it proof.
火药——如果点燃时燃烧了——就被视为证据。
[speaker-02] That rum was good and strong.
那款朗姆酒味道好，酒精度也高。
[speaker-02] See, I ain't got no gunpowder on me, do I?
看，我身上没有火药，对吧？
[speaker-02] But I'm pretty sure you boys will make just as impressive of a sound whe
但我很确定你们这些小伙子也会发出同样令人印象深刻的声音
[speaker-02] n I set your balls on fire.
我让你的睾丸燃烧起来。
[speaker-04] Huh.
哼。
[speaker-04] Or you can just tell me who.
或者你可以直接告诉我是谁。
[speaker-02] Who the fuck y'all really are, and how the hell y'all found us?
你们到底是谁，究竟是怎么找到我们的？
[speaker-02] Look for the last time.
最后一次寻找。
[speaker-03] we have nothing to protect but our honour.
我们没有什么需要保护的，只有荣誉。
[speaker-03] So you can take your cheap horse piss that you call whisky, which,
所以你可以喝下那被称为威士忌的廉价酒，那种酒……
[speaker-03] by the way, is spelt without an e.
顺便说一下，“by the way”没有字母 e。
[speaker-03] It is nothing compared to a single malt scotch,
与单一麦芽苏格兰威士忌相比，这根本不算什么。
[speaker-03] and you can go fuck yourself.
你可以去自个儿滚蛋。
[speaker-04] Hehehehehehehe.
嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿。
[speaker-01] hmm.
嗯。
[speaker-04] What about you?
你呢？
[speaker-02] Me, yeah, no, I love a Jack and Coke.
我啊，不，我喜欢杰克·科克威士忌。
[speaker-05] bro.
兄弟。
[speaker-04] But I do agree with the part where you.
不过我确实同意你那部分的说法。
[speaker-03] Fuck yourself.
去你的。
[speaker-02] All right, y'all ain't got nothing to protect other than your honor.
好的，你们除了荣誉之外没有任何东西可以保护。
[speaker-02] We'll see what happens when we change things up.
我们看看调整一下后会发生什么。
[speaker-04] For me.
对我来说。
[speaker-02] Y'all got three seconds to tell me the truth.
你们只有三秒时间告诉我真相。
[speaker-03] Hurry!
快一点！
[speaker-03] He can't hear you, but.
他听不见你说话，但是。
[speaker-02] I can't talk.
我听不见。
[speaker-02] No, get down.
不，快下来。
[speaker-02] Harry.
哈里。
[speaker-03] Three.
第三。
[speaker-05] Their story checked out.
他们的故事已经结束。
[speaker-08] I opened our doomsday scenario.
我启动了我们的末日场景。
[speaker-05] locker and that umbrella.
储物柜和那把雨伞。
[speaker-08] Gorella was in it.
戈雷拉就在里面。
[speaker-05] Kingsman—it's got our logo on it.
《王牌特工》——上面有我们的标志。
[speaker-05] I'm really sorry.
非常抱歉。
[speaker-02] My apologies, boys.
对不起，各位。
[speaker-02] I hope there ain't no hard feelings.
希望没有任何不满。
[speaker-02] I was just doing my job.
我只是在完成我的工作。
[speaker-02] Welcome to the Statesman, independent intelligence agency.
欢迎来到“国家智者”机构，这是一个独立的情报机构。
[speaker-02] Just like y'all, I reckon,
就像你们一样，我认为。
[speaker-02] but our founders went into the booze business.
但我们的创始人却进入了酒业。
[speaker-02] Thank the sweet Lord above.
感谢天上的仁慈之主。
[speaker-02] This is Ginger Rao.
这是吉妮尔·罗。
[speaker-02] She's our strategy executive.
她是我们的战略执行官。
[speaker-08] Hello.
你好。
[speaker-02] I'm Agent Tequila.
我是Tequila代理。
[speaker-05] This is the part where you untie us.
这是你解开我们关系的地方。
[speaker-03] Thank you.
谢谢。
[speaker-04] How are you?
你好吗？
[speaker-04] Hello.
你好。
[speaker-04] Hurry.
快一点。
[speaker-04] How do you do?
你好吗？
[speaker-04] We met before.
我们之前就见过面。
[speaker-04] Harry, it's okay.
哈里，没事的。
[speaker-04] It's fine.
没关系。
[speaker-04] They—they know that we know you.
他们知道我们知道你。
[speaker-04] I think there must be some mistake.
我觉得肯定有些错误。
[speaker-03] It's been such a long time, Harry.
好久不见啊，哈里。
[speaker-03] I need to get my brogues resoled.
我需要把我的布洛格鞋修好。
[speaker-04] Yeah, and my Oxford.
是的，还有我的牛津鞋。
[speaker-05] are done in as well.
这些也已完成。
[speaker-04] Why are you telling me about your shoes?
为什么你要告诉我关于你的鞋的事？
[speaker-04] I'm a lepidoptrist.
我是一种蝴蝶的专家。
[speaker-04] You're what?
你说什么？
[speaker-04] I study butterflies.
我研究蝴蝶。
[speaker-03] You wanted to be before you joined the army, but.
你原本想在参军之前就这么做，但是……
[speaker-03] Harry, look at me.
哈里，看我。
[speaker-03] It's good to see you.
很高兴见到你。
[speaker-03] We're back soon.
我们很快会回来。
[speaker-03] So these fellas.
这些家伙。
[speaker-02] Right here, our doomsday protocol.
就在这里，我们的末日协议。
[speaker-05] Turns out, our founder's tailor was Kingsmen.
原来，我们的创始人所雇佣的裁缝是Kingsmen人。
[speaker-04] What the fuck have you done to him?
你到底对他做了什么？
[speaker-04] Only.
仅限。
[speaker-05] tried to help him.
试图帮助他。
[speaker-05] He's got retrograde amnesia.
他患有逆行性遗忘症。
[speaker-05] Now we knew from his eyeglasses that he was intelligence.
我们现在从他的眼镜上知道他是个聪明人。
[speaker-05] We just didn't know whose.
我们当时不知道那是谁的东西。
[speaker-03] How did he get here?
他是如何来到这里的？
[speaker-05] What the hell?
什么鬼？
[speaker-04] Do you want to know?
你想知道吗？
[speaker-05] Tequila, I'm getting a crazy spike of extreme low-frequency waves.
龙舌兰，我正经历着极端低频波的剧烈波动。
[speaker-05] Eleven miles from here.
距离这里十一英里。
[speaker-05] I'm going to need you to escort me there immediately.
我需要你立即陪我前往那里。
[speaker-08] The.
[speaker-08] I'm not afraid to die.
我不怕死。
[speaker-08] I'm not a hero.
我不是英雄。
[speaker-05] I need your alpha gel.
我需要你的阿尔法凝胶。
[speaker-02] We'll go check the church.
我们将去检查那座教堂。
[speaker-08] I'm going to have to go.
我必须去一下。
[speaker-08] I'm not sure what I'm doing.
我不确定自己在做什么。
[speaker-08] I'm not a good person.
我不是个好人。
[speaker-05] We developed our alpha gel technology for our own agents.
我们为自己的智能体开发了阿尔法凝胶技术。
[speaker-05] In the event of a headshot, the gel protects the brain.
在遭遇头部伤害时，这种凝胶可以保护大脑。
[speaker-05] Then, in the lab, we use nanites, microbots.
然后，在实验室里，我们使用纳米粒子、微型机器人。
[speaker-05] To repair tissue damage.
修复组织损伤。
[speaker-05] There are side effects:
存在副作用：
[speaker-05] partial amnesia.
部分记忆缺失。
[speaker-05] Regression to the younger self.
回归更年轻的状态。
[speaker-05] With no idea who he was, there was nothing we could do.
由于不知道他是谁，我们无能为力。
[speaker-05] But now you guys are here.
但现在你们都在这里了。
[speaker-05] There's a good chance we can bring him back.
有很大机会我们可以让他回来。
[speaker-04] You're late.
你迟到了。
[speaker-04] Why are you still?
为什么你还在？
[speaker-03] wearing that.
穿着那件衣服。
[speaker-04] Until you get rid.
直到你摆脱它为止。
[speaker-03] Of the perimeter.
关于边界。
[speaker-04] Landmines.
地雷。
[speaker-02] I'll keep wearing it.
我会继续穿它。
[speaker-02] Scared.
害怕了。
[speaker-04] cat.
猫。
[speaker-05] Shut up and sit down.
闭嘴，坐下。
[speaker-04] Let's go.
我们走吧。
[speaker-08] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-04] Crocodile Rock, please.
请给我鳄鱼石。
[speaker-06] Fuck.
该死。
[speaker-04] you!
你！
[speaker-06] Hey!
嘿！
[speaker-04] Hey!
[speaker-04] L ten language.
当前语言：十种语言。
[speaker-04] Well, as Fabi.
好吧，就像法比说的那样。
[speaker-05] Irena says, "Your catalog is.
伊雷娜说：“你的目录是。”
[speaker-04] I think I want to hear some Gershwin.
我想想听一些格什温的歌。
[speaker-04] I still can't believe you've got away with it.
我还是不敢相信你竟然能蒙混过关。
[speaker-03] We're kidnapping out in jail.
我们正在监狱里绑架人。
[speaker-02] John.
约翰。
[speaker-03] I know, but with Valentine abducting.
我知道，但 Valentine在绑架人。
[speaker-05] Those celebrities—it seems.
那些名人——似乎是这样。
[speaker-02] silly not to take advantage.
不利用机会真是愚蠢。
[speaker-05] of the confusion.
关于混乱的情况。
[speaker-04] Has Elton got the?
埃尔顿得到了吗？
[speaker-03] I've got the blue rash.
我长了蓝色的皮疹。
[speaker-04] Lights.
灯光。
[speaker-04] Hey, Elton, have you been a bad boy again?
嘿，埃尔顿，你又表现得像个坏孩子吗？
[speaker-04] You're lying.
你在撒谎。
[speaker-04] Look at your hands.
看看你的手。
[speaker-03] What is it's proof that my plan is.
什么是证明我的计划有效的证据？
[speaker-04] Is gonna work.
会成功的。
[speaker-05] Also, the first sign of a slow and horrible death.
此外，这是缓慢而痛苦的死亡的第一个迹象。
[speaker-05] Don't worry.
不用担心。
[speaker-05] I can fix it.
我可以修复它。
[speaker-04] Tell me who you partied with.
请告诉我你和谁一起聚会。
[speaker-04] It was Angel.
那是安吉尔。
[speaker-03] Huh.
嗯。
[speaker-04] Not very angelic.
不太像天使的样子。
[speaker-04] Gonna have to clip his wings.
必须剪掉他的翅膀。
[speaker-06] I'm sorry.
对不起。
[speaker-08] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-08] I'm gonna make you mine.
我会让你成为我的。
[speaker-08] The.
那个。
[speaker-02] Close the door behind you.
关上你身后的门。
[speaker-03] At what point are you going to start behaving like a statesman, DeKayla?
你什么时候才能像政治家一样行事，德凯拉？
[speaker-03] You want to go back to being a rodeo clown?
你想变回牛仔竞技表演的小丑吗？
[speaker-02] I apologize, sir.
对不起，先生。
[speaker-03] I'm champagne.
我是香槟。
[speaker-03] But anyone who knows what's good for 'em.
但任何知道如何让他们过得更好的人。
[speaker-03] Calls me a champ.
称我为香槟。
[speaker-03] Sorry for your troubles.
对不起给您带来麻烦。
[speaker-03] As your American cousins.
作为您的美国表亲。
[speaker-03] I'm placing all the statesman's considerably larger resources at your di
我将所有政治家的更大资源都投入到了您的项目中
[speaker-03] sposal.
[speaker-03] Can you imagine us in the clothing business?
你能想象我们在服装行业的情况吗？
[speaker-03] Now, how can I help you?
现在，我能为您提供什么帮助？
[speaker-03] First of all.
首先。
[speaker-02] I've got to thank.
我必须表示感谢。
[speaker-04] you for saving Agent Galahad.
感谢您为 Galahad 代理人保存数据。
[speaker-03] You said that you were Galahad.
您说您是 Galahad。
[speaker-03] Oh no, he's talking.
哦，不，他正在说话。
[speaker-02] about the butterfly guy.
关于那个蝴蝶人。
[speaker-02] That used to be his handle.
那曾经是他的用户名。
[speaker-02] Oh, got it.
哦，明白了。
[speaker-03] Galahad always said, "You.
Galahad总是说：“你。”
[speaker-02] You've got to look at the bigger picture.
你得从整体角度来看待这件事。
[speaker-02] Ask why, as well as who.
询问原因和询问是谁。
[speaker-02] So, if someone wanted to take out Kingsman,
那么，如果有人想推出《王牌特工》的话，
[speaker-02] then they've got to be planning something major.
那么他们肯定正在策划什么重大计划。
[speaker-03] So, what do you know?
那么，你知道些什么呢？
[speaker-03] They're a drug cartel.
他们是个毒品贩毒集团。
[speaker-02] We think the name Golden Circle keeps coming up.
我们认为“金环”这个名称频繁出现。
[speaker-03] We'll look into them.
我们将调查它们。
[speaker-03] What else?
还有什么？
[speaker-03] One of our former.
我们以前的人之一。
[speaker-02] All Matrines is working with them.
All Matrines正在与他们合作。
[speaker-02] Charlie Hesketh.
查理·赫斯凯斯。
[speaker-02] Total prick!
总得解决一下！
[speaker-02] You got an impression?
你有什么印象吗？
[speaker-03] Any promising leads, Homer?
有什么有希望的线索吗，霍默？
[speaker-03] His ex-girlfriend.
他的前女友。
[speaker-02] I've been tracking her through social media.
我通过社交媒体一直在关注她。
[speaker-02] We believe she's still in contact with him.
我们认为她仍然与他有联系。
[speaker-02] And she's going to Glastonbury Music Festival.
她即将参加格拉斯顿伯里音乐节。
[speaker-03] Oh, good.
哦，太好了。
[speaker-03] Agent Tequila, break out your dancing shoes.
特基拉Agent，穿上你的舞鞋吧。
[speaker-03] You have a new mission.
你有一个新的任务。
[speaker-03] Yes, sir.
是的，先生。
[speaker-03] Hold up.
等等。
[speaker-03] You feeling okay?
你感觉好吗？
[speaker-03] I'm a little tired.
我有点累了。
[speaker-04] Fine.
好的。
[speaker-04] Thanks.
谢谢。
[speaker-02] Galahad, you ready?
加勒哈德，你准备好了吗？
[speaker-02] Your face.
你的脸。
[speaker-03] He got.
他好了。
[speaker-02] What the.
什么啊。
[speaker-06] Fuck.
该死。
[speaker-04] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-03] Yeah.
是的。
[speaker-03] Head to sick bay.
去病室去。
[speaker-03] Have ginger check you out.
让姜恩看看你吧。
[speaker-04] Hey.
嘿。
[speaker-03] Give them your glasses.
把你的眼镜给他们。
[speaker-03] You're in luck, kid.
你真幸运，孩子。
[speaker-03] Put 'em on.
戴上它们。
[speaker-03] You'd get our finest senior agent to join you instead.
你会得到我们最优秀的资深代理人来加入你。
[speaker-03] Right now, he's in our New York office.
目前，他在我们纽约办公室工作。
[speaker-03] Yelahad meat agent whiskey.
耶拉哈德肉品代理威士忌。
[speaker-01] Kid.
孩子。
[speaker-02] Looks like we're hooking up with a chick.
看来我们要和个女孩约会了。
[speaker-04] at a rock concert.
在摇滚音乐会上。
[speaker-02] My favorite kind of mission.
我最喜欢的任务类型。
[speaker-04] I'm sending my jet to pick you up.
我正在派我的飞机来接你。
[speaker-05] We've dealt with this kind of amnesia before.
我们之前处理过这种失忆情况。
[speaker-05] Harry's like a computer that needs to be rebooted.
哈里就像一台需要重启的电脑。
[speaker-05] We need to recreate a shock or trauma from his past.
我们需要重现他过去所经历的震惊或创伤。
[speaker-05] To trigger his memory.
触发他的记忆。
[speaker-03] I hope you're right.
我希望你是对的。
[speaker-04] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-06] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-08] Seems to be some sort of problem here.
似乎这里有些问题。
[speaker-08] Help!
救命！
[speaker-08] Somebody!
有人！
[speaker-08] What's going on?
怎么了？
[speaker-08] Help me!
救命！
[speaker-08] No!
不！
[speaker-08] Oh God!
哦，天哪！
[speaker-08] No.
不！
[speaker-08] Dude.
兄弟。
[speaker-06] Get him out now.
现在就把他救出来。
[speaker-05] His instincts are going to kick in.
他的直觉会立刻发挥作用。
[speaker-08] Oh!
哦！
[speaker-08] No, I'm sorry to do this.
不，很抱歉我无法做到这一点。
[speaker-08] Are you okay?
你还好吗？
[speaker-03] What happened, Harry?
怎么了，哈里？
[speaker-03] You forgot.
你忘了。
[speaker-04] who you are?
你是谁？
[speaker-04] We thought this might jog your memory.
我们以为这可能会唤起你的记忆。
[speaker-04] Look, when you were young, you had a choice.
看，你年轻的时候，是有选择权的。
[speaker-04] To either be a lepidopterist or to join the army, you chose.
要么成为鳞翅目昆虫学家，要么参军，这就是你的选择。
[speaker-04] The army that led to Kingsmen.
导致“国王党人”出现的军队。
[speaker-04] You became a Kingsmen agent.
你成为了 Kingsmen 的代理人。
[speaker-04] I doubt whether I'd work for anyone who drowns their employees.
我怀疑自己是否愿意为那些让员工溺死的企业工作。
[speaker-04] I want to go home.
我想回家。
[speaker-04] Want my butterfly collection.
想要我的蝴蝶收藏。
[speaker-04] Want to see mother?
想见母亲吗？
[speaker-05] There's nothing more we can do.
我们无能为力了。
[speaker-05] It's time to let him go.
是时候放他走了。
[speaker-02] Babe, I wish I could stay longer,
宝贝，我希望能多待一会儿。
[speaker-02] but I've got to get on with this mission.
但我必须继续完成这项任务。
[speaker-02] Wait!
等等！
[speaker-05] Before.
之前。
[speaker-02] you go.
你走吧。
[speaker-05] I want to show you something.
我想给你展示一些东西。
[speaker-05] I know he could never replace JB, but.
我知道他永远无法取代 JB，但是……
[speaker-04] Oh my!
哦，天哪！
[speaker-02] I hope.
我希望。
[speaker-05] He might make you happy.
他可能会让你开心。
[speaker-03] And give you.
并给你。
[speaker-05] another reason to come back home soon.
另一个原因让我很快回家。
[speaker-02] I love him.
我喜欢他。
[speaker-02] But I don't need another reason to come home.
但我不需要另一个理由才能回家。
[speaker-04] I apologize.
对不起。
[speaker-04] Just waiting for my friend.
正在等待我的朋友。
[speaker-02] I'll be back as soon as I can.
我会尽快回来。
[speaker-02] Promise.
承诺。
[speaker-05] Got to go.
得走了。
[speaker-05] Save the world.
拯救世界。
[speaker-02] Well.
嗯。
[speaker-05] If you save the world.
如果你拯救世界的话。
[speaker-05] You know what that means.
你知道那意味着什么。
[speaker-05] Yeah, all right.
是的，好的。
[speaker-02] Bye, buddy.
再见，朋友。
[speaker-02] Got the passes from my contact.
从我的联系人那里得到了通行证。
[speaker-02] You're gonna love Glastonbury.
你会喜欢格拉斯顿伯里音乐节的。
[speaker-04] Well, that's the easy part, kid.
嗯，那是容易的部分，孩子。
[speaker-04] Take a look in the glove box.
查看手套箱里的情况。
[speaker-02] Fucking hell, bro!
该死，兄弟！
[speaker-02] Thought everything was supposed to be bigger in America.
原本以为在美国的一切都会更宏大。
[speaker-02] Is this why you overcompensate with these massive cars?
这就是你用这些大车来过度补偿的原因吗？
[speaker-04] On your finger, the surveillance tracker is in the tip.
在手指上，监控追踪器位于指尖处。
[speaker-04] Apply light pressure for three seconds to release it.
施加轻微压力三秒后释放即可。
[speaker-08] Now what's right?
现在怎么样？
[speaker-08] I miss you.
我想你。
[speaker-02] Okay, so according to her Instagram feed,
好的，根据她的 Instagram 动态来看……
[speaker-02] Charlie's ex-girlfriend is up ahead at the VIP bar.
查理的前女友正在VIP酒吧前面。
[speaker-02] Which one of us is going to plant the tracker?
我们当中谁会安装那个追踪器呢？
[speaker-02] Blang's boy.
布兰克的男孩。
[speaker-03] Yeah, that's fine.
是的，没问题的。
[speaker-04] I say we both make an approach.
我们俩一起尝试一下吧。
[speaker-04] Whoever gets on best goes for it.
谁进展得最好，就由谁来行动。
[speaker-02] It doesn't have to be a competition, bruv.
不必非要竞争啊，兄弟。
[speaker-02] Why don't we just go up to her, shake her hand, pat her on the back,
我们直接走到她面前，和她握手，拍拍她的背怎么样？
[speaker-02] You know, job done.
你知道，任务完成了。
[speaker-04] A hand is not a mucous membrane, Eggsy.
手不是黏膜，埃格斯。
[speaker-04] Now there's the back.
现在在背后。
[speaker-04] They teach you anything at Kingsman.
在Kingsman学校，他们会教你任何东西。
[speaker-04] You talking about?
你在说什么？
[speaker-02] Wow.
哇。
[speaker-04] Our trackers are designed to enter the bloodstream.
我们的追踪器被设计成可以进入血液流。
[speaker-04] They circulate harmlessly, providing full audio and GPS.
它们无害地传播着信息，同时提供完整的音频和GPS数据。
[speaker-02] Mucus membrane—that's like up the nose, isn't it?
黏膜——就是鼻子里的那层，对吧？
[speaker-02] What the fuck am I going to do?
我到底要做什么啊？
[speaker-02] Stick a finger.
插一根手指。
[speaker-02] It's not just inside the nose, is it?
不是只存在于鼻子里面，对吧？
[speaker-04] Excellent!
很好！
[speaker-04] Fuck.
靠。
[speaker-04] first crack.
第一次突破。
[speaker-04] Watch and learn, buddy.
观看学习吧，朋友。
[speaker-06] We'll have a look.
我们稍后看看吧。
[speaker-02] Good luck.
祝你好运。
[speaker-08] There you go, ma'am.
请收下，女士。
[speaker-05] Miss, how big?
女士，有多大？
[speaker-04] I beg your pardon.
请原谅我的错误。
[speaker-04] Now, I don't want to pester you,
现在，我不想打扰您。
[speaker-04] but I just have to know what time are you playing?
但我只是想知道你什么时候玩？
[speaker-05] I'm not in a band.
我不是在乐队里。
[speaker-05] My God, who did you think I was?
天哪，你以为我是谁啊？
[speaker-05] Please don't say someone ghastly.
请不要说某人是可怕的。
[speaker-04] like a fool.
像个傻子一样。
[speaker-04] I just assumed that a woman with your.
我只是假设有一个女人拥有你的特质。
[speaker-04] Charisma.
魅力。
[speaker-04] Well, she just had to be somebody.
嗯，她总得成为某个人吧。
[speaker-05] Right.
正确。
[speaker-05] Thank you.
谢谢。
[speaker-04] I know you didn't mean to make me feel like a dumbass.
我知道你不是故意让我觉得自己像个笨蛋。
[speaker-04] So I'll let you make it up to me by letting me buy you a drink.
那么我就请你们喝一杯来补偿我吧。
[speaker-05] Follow my finger.
跟随我的手指。
[speaker-04] What are we doing?
我们在做什么？
[speaker-05] Swiping to the left.
向左滑动。
[speaker-05] What you don't do Tinder in America?
在美国，在 Tinder 上不能做什么？
[speaker-05] Tinder what?
Tinder是什么？
[speaker-04] You know, I think he's.
你知道，我觉得他是。
[speaker-02] It's probably a generational thing.
这可能是一种代际差异导致的现象。
[speaker-02] It translates as "Go away, old man.
去吧，老头子。
[speaker-04] Be good.
好好表现。
[speaker-04] Be cool.
保持冷静。
[speaker-04] Bye.
再见。
[speaker-02] Thank you for that.
谢谢。
[speaker-05] I'm Clara.
我是克拉拉。
[speaker-05] River.
河流。
[speaker-02] Bloody hell!
该死！
[speaker-02] Is that the time?
是时候了吗？
[speaker-02] Do you know what?
你知道吗？
[speaker-02] I'm so jet lagged.
我太有时差了。
[speaker-02] I don't know if I'm coming or going.
我不知道自己是来还是走。
[speaker-02] Where have you been?
你去了哪里？
[speaker-05] anywhere nice?
任何地方都好吗？
[speaker-05] South America.
南美洲。
[speaker-02] Been spending a bit of time out there, training with the shaman,
在那里待了一段时间，与萨满一起进行训练。
[speaker-02] trying to really connect with my spirit animal.
试图真正与我的守护灵建立联系。
[speaker-05] Yeah, I'm a crow.
是的，我是一只乌鸦。
[speaker-02] And hang on, let me guess.
等等，让我猜一下。
[speaker-02] Jag you up.
激励你。
[speaker-03] What?
什么？
[speaker-02] Oh my God.
哦，天哪。
[speaker-05] How would you?
你会怎么想？
[speaker-02] How do you even know?
你究竟是怎么知道的？
[speaker-05] Look, it totally is.
看吧，确实如此。
[speaker-05] Check it out.
看看吧。
[speaker-02] In a Mokso, black Jaguar, very nice, Noah.
在莫克索号上，那是一辆黑色的美洲虎，非常不错，诺亚。
[speaker-05] I want to buy you a drink.
我想请你喝一杯。
[speaker-05] Excuse me.
打扰一下。
[speaker-04] Exy sent this from Glastonbury.
埃克西从格拉斯顿伯里发来此信息。
[speaker-04] And #blue_rash is trending on Twitter.
而且 #blue_rash 在推特上很流行。
[speaker-04] Have you found any correlation between these cases?
您发现这些案例之间存在任何关联吗？
[speaker-05] Only recreational drug use.
仅涉及娱乐性药物使用。
[speaker-05] Not very statesmanlike.
不太符合政治家应有的作风。
[speaker-05] Tequila here.
这里是龙舌兰酒。
[speaker-05] He is our resident bad boy.
他是我们的模范坏学生。
[speaker-04] You don't think this could be related to the golden circle?
你认为这可能与“金色圆圈”有关吗？
[speaker-05] A drug cartel poisoning its customers.
一个毒品集团正在毒害其客户。
[speaker-05] Does it make sense?
有道理吗？
[speaker-06] 嗯。
[speaker-04] Poppy, would you pass your sugar?
Poppy，你能把糖递给我吗？
[speaker-02] Some sugar, please.
请给我一些糖。
[speaker-05] but it's really bad for you.
但这对你真的很不利。
[speaker-05] Eight times more addictive than cocaine.
比可卡因成瘾性高八倍。
[speaker-05] Five times more likely to cause.
可能性增加五倍。
[speaker-05] Death, but it's legal.
死亡，但这是合法的。
[speaker-05] So you know, you go ahead, knock yourself out.
所以你懂的，你继续吧，尽情享受吧。
[speaker-05] Don't get me started on tobacco and alcohol.
别跟我提烟草和酒精。
[speaker-05] You peddle that stuff, and you're in the Fortune Five Hundred.
你贩卖那种东西，就能跻身财富五百人榜。
[speaker-05] No, I'm out here.
不，我在这里。
[speaker-05] Hiding in the middle of nowhere, homesick.
躲在偏僻的地方，感到思乡。
[speaker-05] Because I sell drugs.
因为我贩卖毒品。
[speaker-05] Oh, cops.
哦，警察啊。
[speaker-02] You're doing this because you're homesick.
你这么做是因为感到思乡。
[speaker-02] Yes.
是的。
[speaker-05] I want freedom.
我想要自由。
[speaker-05] I want fame.
我想要名声。
[speaker-05] Our profits were two hundred and fifty billion dollars last year.
去年我们的利润达到了二百五十十亿美元。
[speaker-05] I am the most successful businesswoman in the world, but nobody.
我是世界上最成功的商界女性，但无人知晓。
[speaker-05] knows who I am.
知道我是谁。
[speaker-04] It's not long now, eh.
现在时间不长，对吧。
[speaker-02] Thank you.
谢谢。
[speaker-04] Sorry to interrupt you.
很抱歉打扰您。
[speaker-02] You wanted to see me.
你想见我。
[speaker-04] Madam Poppy.
波比女士。
[speaker-02] Yes, sing.
是的，唱吧。
[speaker-05] Yes, Angel.
是的，天使。
[speaker-05] In the Golden Circle, we do not sample the merchandise, and we do not.
在金环区域，我们不会采集商品，也不会进行相关操作。
[speaker-05] Break the rules,
打破规则，
[speaker-05] which is why I have invested in robots because they are so much more.
因此我投资了机器人，因为它们优势明显。
[speaker-05] Reliable and trustworthy than human beings.
比人类更可靠、更值得信赖。
[speaker-06] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-08] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-08] Oh!
哦！
[speaker-08] No!
不！
[speaker-06] Oh!
哦！
[speaker-06] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-08] Oh.
[speaker-08] Oh, what!
哦，什么！
[speaker-08] Whoa!
哇！
[speaker-08] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-05] Sorry, we never found your friends.
抱歉，我们没有找到您的朋友。
[speaker-02] Well, we all go on our separate journeys, but ultimately,
嗯，我们各自走向不同的道路，但归根结底，
[speaker-02] we'll all arrive at the same destination.
我们都会到达同一个目的地。
[speaker-03] Should we check my tent?
我们应该检查我的帐篷吗？
[speaker-05] See if they're there.
看看他们是否在那里。
[speaker-06] Come on.
来吧。
[speaker-05] Wow.
哇。
[speaker-02] This is amazing.
这太令人惊叹了。
[speaker-05] Come on.
来吧。
[speaker-04] You know what?
你知道吗？
[speaker-02] Busting for a pee, actually.
其实是在努力小便。
[speaker-02] You can do it on me.
你可以依靠我来完成这件事。
[speaker-05] if you want.
如果你愿意。
[speaker-06] Uh.
嗯。
[speaker-02] Maybe in a bit.
也许稍后吧。
[speaker-02] Give me a sec, yeah.
给我一点时间，好的。
[speaker-05] Okay, but hurry up, River.
好的，但快一点吧，River。
[speaker-05] Been waiting all night for you to at least kiss me.
整晚都在等待你至少吻我一下。
[speaker-06] Yeah.
是的。
[speaker-02] Hi, babe.
嗨，宝贝。
[speaker-02] Bit of a nightmare.
有点像一场噩梦。
[speaker-02] I've got to sleep with a target,
我得和目标对象一起睡觉。
[speaker-02] but I won't do it unless you agree that it's all right.
但除非你同意这没问题，否则我不会这么做。
[speaker-05] You gotta be fucking kidding!
你一定在开玩笑吧！
[speaker-05] Where was I?
我在哪里？
[speaker-05] Target practice.
目标练习。
[speaker-02] surely it's better that I'm honest with you rather than me doing it and
显然，对你诚实比我自己去做要好得多。
[speaker-02] not telling you.
没有告诉你。
[speaker-02] Kind of got a bit of a save the world situation here.
有点像在进行一场拯救世界的行动。
[speaker-05] How the fuck is screwing someone going to save the world?
到底怎么通过折磨别人来拯救世界呢？
[speaker-02] It's bit complicated, but trust me,
有点复杂，但相信我吧。
[speaker-02] I would not be doing it if I didn't have to.
如果不需要的话，我就不会这么做。
[speaker-06] Babe, please.
亲爱的，拜托了。
[speaker-02] I love you are the person that I want to spend the rest of my life with
我爱你，是我想与之共度余生的人
[speaker-05] Is that a proposal?
那是提议吗？
[speaker-01] Because I.
因为我。
[speaker-05] I think I gave you my permission.
我觉得我已经同意了。
[speaker-05] Having that security, knowing that we were committed.
拥有那种安全感，知道我们已承诺对方。
[speaker-06] You.
你。
[speaker-05] In that context, yeah, I'd feel different.
在那种情况下，是的，我的感受会不同。
[speaker-03] Right.
正确。
[speaker-03] What.
什么。
[speaker-01] Well, I mean, I mean.
嗯，我的意思是，就是那样。
[speaker-02] I want to be with you, but being a public figure, babe, like a prince,
我想和你在一起，但作为公众人物，亲爱的，就像王子一样。
[speaker-02] is.
是。
[speaker-02] Was a bit of a factor, you know, what with my job and stuff.
这确实是一个因素，你知道的，考虑到我的工作等等。
[speaker-02] Come on!
来吧！
[speaker-02] Okay, look, we need to talk about this.
好的，听着，我们需要讨论这个问题。
[speaker-02] Properly, just give me five minutes, okay?
好吧，就给我五分钟吧，行吗？
[speaker-05] Don't put yourself down, Exy.
不要自我贬低，Exy。
[speaker-05] I'm sure you can last longer than that.
我相信你肯定能坚持更长时间。
[speaker-05] What's the matter?
怎么了？
[speaker-05] Nothing.
无。
[speaker-02] I just feel that our spirit animals need more time to get in sync.
我觉得我们的精神动物需要更多时间才能协调一致。
[speaker-02] And find a harmonious bond on the spiritual plane.
在精神层面建立一种和谐的关系。
[speaker-02] Totally.
完全同意。
[speaker-02] Yeah.
是的。
[speaker-02] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-05] We could just.
我们完全可以如此。
[speaker-05] Fuck.
该死。
[speaker-02] Clara, I don't think I can.
克拉拉，我觉得我做不到。
[speaker-02] Do you know what?
你知道吗？
[speaker-02] My crow is looking for a place to nest.
我的乌鸦正在寻找一个筑巢的地方。
[speaker-08] I'm not sure if I can do this.
我不确定自己能否做到这一点。
[speaker-08] I'm not afraid of heights.
我不怕高。
[speaker-08] I'm not a man.
我不是男人。
[speaker-04] Good work, Eggsy.
好工作，埃格斯。
[speaker-04] Tracker fully functional.
追踪器完全可用。
[speaker-05] Don't worry.
不用担心。
[speaker-05] I've been through this with whiskey before.
我之前用威士忌试过这种方法。
[speaker-05] Nice to be working with an agent who knows what he's doing.
很高兴能与一个明白自己职责的人合作。
[speaker-06] Hmm.
嗯。
[speaker-01] Wow, Mr.
哇，先生
[speaker-01] Creed.
Creed。
[speaker-05] Crow, my turn.
Crow，我的回合。
[speaker-05] I'm sorry.
对不起。
[speaker-02] I'm in a relationship.
我在恋爱中。
[speaker-02] That's adorable.
那太可爱了。
[speaker-05] Listen.
听好了。
[speaker-05] So am I.
我也是。
[speaker-05] What happens at Glaston stays.
在格拉斯顿停留期间会发生什么。
[speaker-05] In Gloucester.
在格洛斯特。
[speaker-02] I can't.
我做不到。
[speaker-02] Bye, Clara.
再见，克拉拉。
[speaker-05] This is Princess T.
这是T公主。
[speaker-05] Please leave a message.
请留下一条消息。
[speaker-02] Morton Manor Hotel.
莫顿庄园酒店。
[speaker-02] Yeah, can you put me through to Princess Tildy, please?
是的，请帮我转接给Tildy公主吧。
[speaker-02] Oh, actually, sir, I'm just looking at my computer,
哦，实际上，先生，我正在看我的电脑。
[speaker-02] and I'm afraid that the princess has already checked out.
而且我担心公主已经退房了。
[speaker-02] Harry.
哈里。
[speaker-02] What's going on?
怎么了？
[speaker-02] I'm just packing.
我正在收拾东西。
[speaker-02] These lovely toiletries, Mellin,
这些漂亮的洗漱用品，Mellin。
[speaker-02] very kindly gave me as a leaving present.
非常友善地送了我一份作为离开的礼物。
[speaker-02] Try this aftershave.
试试这种须后水吧。
[speaker-02] Yeah, I know, Harry.
是的，我知道，哈里。
[speaker-02] I'm wearing it.
我正在穿它。
[speaker-02] You can't just give up.
你不能轻易放弃。
[speaker-03] Divorce.
离婚。
[speaker-04] No, on the contrary, I am about to achieve my dream.
不，相反，我即将实现我的梦想。
[speaker-02] Researching rare butterflies alongside some of the finest minds in entom
与一些最优秀的昆虫学专家一起研究稀有蝴蝶
[speaker-02] ology.
学科。
[speaker-02] You know, you may as well have me stuck upon this wall.
你知道，你不妨把我钉在这面墙上吧。
[speaker-02] 'Cause you're never gonna find a butterfly more interesting than me.
因为你永远找不到比我更有趣的蝴蝶。
[speaker-02] Sorry.
对不起。
[speaker-02] When you and I first met.
当你和我第一次见面时。
[speaker-02] I was just like a maggot.
我就像一只蛆一样。
[speaker-02] Maggots turn into flies.
蛆会变成苍蝇。
[speaker-04] Perhaps you mean lava.
或许你指的是岩浆。
[speaker-02] Whatever.
随便吧。
[speaker-02] The point is, everyone wanted to squash me.
关键在于，每个人都想压制我。
[speaker-02] But not you helped me to become a caterpillar.
但不是你帮助我变成了毛毛虫。
[speaker-02] And now I've got wings.
现在我有翅膀了。
[speaker-02] I'm flying higher than I ever dreamed, and that's all thanks to you.
我正在飞得比想象中还要高，这全都是你的功劳。
[speaker-04] I hate to seem rude, but I need to finish packing and get some sleep.
我不想显得无礼，但得把东西收拾好，再睡一会儿。
[speaker-02] Harry, you can't just walk away.
哈里，你不能就这么离开。
[speaker-02] Kingsman needs you.
金斯曼需要你。
[speaker-04] The whole world needs you.
全世界都需要你。
[speaker-02] He needs you.
他需要你。
[speaker-02] I need you.
我需要你。
[speaker-04] Eggie.
埃吉。
[speaker-04] Whoever the Harry was that you knew, he's gone.
无论你认识的哈里是谁，他已经离开了。
[speaker-04] I'm afraid.
我害怕。
[speaker-04] Goodbye.
再见。
[speaker-03] You fill up my sails.
你撑起了我的帆。
[speaker-02] This little martini.
这杯小马提尼酒。
[speaker-05] He's in Kentucky.
他住在肯塔基州。
[speaker-02] Fair enough.
说得有道理。
[speaker-04] Here's to you, Eggsy.
为你干杯，Eggsy。
[speaker-04] You're exactly what Kingsman needs.
你正是金斯曼所需要的那个人。
[speaker-05] Ocean.
海洋。
[speaker-08] This is Princess Tea.
这是 Princess Tea。
[speaker-05] Please leave a message.
请留下一条消息。
[speaker-04] Come to me.
来我这里。
[speaker-02] Can I have another martini, please?
请再给我来一杯马提尼酒。
[speaker-02] Sure.
当然。
[speaker-05] Thanks.
谢谢。
[speaker-02] Come, let me love.
来吧，让我爱你。
[speaker-07] I love you.
我爱你。
[speaker-02] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-05] Give up.
放弃。
[speaker-02] You know what?
你知道吗？
[speaker-02] That was the best martini I've ever had.
这是我喝过最棒的马提尼酒。
[speaker-02] Keep your change.
保留零钱。
[speaker-02] Thanks.
谢谢。
[speaker-05] So I don't.
所以我不做。
[speaker-02] Just thought I'd bring you a little leaving present.
我想给你带一份小礼物作为告别。
[speaker-02] What do you think?
你觉得怎么样？
[speaker-02] He's lovely, isn't he?
他真可爱，对吧？
[speaker-02] Would you like to hold him?
你想留住他吗？
[speaker-01] No.
无。
[speaker-01] He.
他。
[speaker-02] Do you think I should shoot him?
你觉得我应该杀了他吗？
[speaker-04] You're quite mad.
你真疯狂。
[speaker-04] What's the problem?
有什么问题吗？
[speaker-02] No, you can't.
不，你不能这么做。
[speaker-03] No, you'll have to shoot me.
不，你必须开枪打我。
[speaker-03] What to shoot you?
该射击你什么？
[speaker-02] Well, we'll shoot you.
好吧，我们会开枪打你。
[speaker-02] No one's sick enough to shoot a puppy.
没有人病得足以射杀一只小狗。
[speaker-04] Well, what about you, Harry?
那么，你呢，哈利？
[speaker-02] you were sick enough to shoot a puppy.
你病得足以射杀一只小狗。
[speaker-02] Do you remember?
你还记得吗？
[speaker-06] I'm not going to let you get away with this.
我不会让你得逞。
[speaker-02] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-08] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-01] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-08] Oh.
[speaker-08] I'm not a good person.
我不是个好人。
[speaker-08] I'm not a man.
[speaker-02] It was a blank.
它是一片空白。
[speaker-02] Yes, it was a fucking blank.
是的，它简直一片空白。
[speaker-02] That's right.
没错。
[speaker-02] It was a blank.
它是一片空白。
[speaker-02] I would never hurt Mr.
我永远不会伤害先生。
[speaker-02] Yes, Harry.
是的，哈里。
[speaker-02] He lived to a ripe old age.
他活到了高龄。
[speaker-02] He died of pancreatic cancer.
他因胰腺癌去世。
[speaker-04] You're not, Mr.
您不是，先生。
[speaker-04] Pickle.
泡菜。
[speaker-04] Exi.
例如。
[speaker-02] Hello, Harry.
你好，哈里。
[speaker-06] Nixie.
尼克斯。
[speaker-04] Valentine has to be stopped.
必须阻止瓦伦丁。
[speaker-04] No, he has a device.
不，他有一个设备。
[speaker-04] It's all right.
没关系。
[speaker-04] Don't worry.
不用担心。
[speaker-02] We got a lot of catching up to do.
我们有很多事情需要弥补。
[speaker-04] Well.
好的。
[speaker-06] I suppose I should.
我认为应该如此。
[speaker-03] cancel that taxi.
取消那辆出租车。
[speaker-04] Yes.
是的。
[speaker-04] If you don't mind.
如果你不介意的话。
[speaker-04] Manny.
曼尼。
[speaker-03] Welcome back.
欢迎回来。
[speaker-03] Galahad.
加勒哈德。
[speaker-06] Now we finish.
现在结束。
[speaker-02] the debrief, Harry.
汇报会，哈里。
[speaker-02] Here's a couple of welcome back gifts.
这里有几份欢迎回来的礼物。
[speaker-02] First up.
首先。
[speaker-02] Brand new Kingsman watch.
全新的金斯曼手表。
[speaker-02] Advanced software;
高级软件；
[speaker-02] it can hack into anything with a microchip.
它可以通过微芯片侵入任何设备。
[speaker-02] It is the bollock.
这就是那个球。
[speaker-02] And, well.
而且，嗯。
[speaker-03] I made you these.
我做了这些给你。
[speaker-04] Ah.
啊。
[speaker-01] I'm not sure.
我不确定。
[speaker-04] Thank you, Merlin.
谢谢你，梅林。
[speaker-02] How do I look?
我看起来怎么样？
[speaker-03] Like some faggot looking for an eye, fucking.
就像某个长相丑陋的人在寻找目标一样，真恶心。
[speaker-02] In.
正在输入中。
[speaker-03] Now, why don't you get out of our bar?
现在，你为什么不离开我们的酒吧呢？
[speaker-03] Before I take out your other one.
在我拿出你的另一个东西之前。
[speaker-03] Now, is that anyway to welcome a visitor?
现在，这算是一种欢迎访客的方式吗？
[speaker-04] from out of town, moonshine.
来自外地，自制酒精。
[speaker-03] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-03] Suck my southern dick.
吸我的南方人阴茎。
[speaker-03] Bitch.
贱人。
[speaker-04] Oh, I don't think that'll be necessary.
哦，我觉得不需要那样做。
[speaker-04] Good, Jason.
好的，杰森。
[speaker-03] Well.
好吧。
[speaker-03] What are you ladies waiting for?
你们女士们还在等什么？
[speaker-04] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-06] Maketh.
马克思。
[speaker-04] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-04] Man.
男人。
[speaker-06] Do you know what that means?
你知道那是什么意思吗？
[speaker-04] Then let me teach you a lesson.
那么让我来给你上一课吧。
[speaker-01] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-08] I'm not a man.
我不是男人。
[speaker-04] Are we going to stand around here all day, or are we going to?
我们是要在这里站一整天，还是有其他安排呢？
[speaker-04] Oh, you picked the wrong bag.
哦，你选错了袋子。
[speaker-08] Yeah!
耶！
[speaker-08] Oh!
哦！
[speaker-08] Ah!
啊！
[speaker-06] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-08] Oh.
[speaker-08] Oh!
哦！
[speaker-03] Well, pick 'em up.
好吧，把它们拿起来。
[speaker-03] Now that is not what I call a Kentucky welcome.
这真不叫肯塔基式的欢迎方式。
[speaker-03] Manners maketh man.
礼貌成就人。
[speaker-03] Let me translate that for you.
让我来为您翻译那部分内容。
[speaker-08] Ah!
啊！
[speaker-03] No!
不！
[speaker-08] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-06] Oh!
哦！
[speaker-08] Ah!
啊！
[speaker-08] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-08] Ah!
啊！
[speaker-04] What's wrong with me, Melly?
怎么了，Melly？
[speaker-04] I thought you fixed me.
我以为你修好了我。
[speaker-04] Well, we rebuilt.
嗯，我们重新构建好了。
[speaker-03] Built your neural pathways,
构建了你的神经通路，
[speaker-03] but it'll take time to get your coordination back.
但恢复你的协调能力还需要一些时间。
[speaker-08] Ah!
啊！
[speaker-06] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-08] Oh.
[speaker-08] Oh!
哦！
[speaker-08] And the phantom.
还有那个幻影。
[speaker-04] You will experience.
你会有所体验。
[speaker-03] episodes, lapses of clarity.
剧集，意识模糊的时刻。
[speaker-03] You'll be back to normal soon.
你很快就会恢复正常状态。
[speaker-06] Oh!
哦！
[speaker-06] Ah!
啊！
[speaker-06] Ah.
啊。
[speaker-08] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-08] Oh!
哦！
[speaker-06] No.
不。
[speaker-08] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-06] Ooh.
[speaker-03] I feel like a tornado in a trailer park.
我感觉像拖车公园里的龙卷风。
[speaker-06] Golden circle.
金环。
[speaker-05] President, my name is Poppy Adams.
总统，我的名字是波比·亚当斯。
[speaker-05] I believe the UN has no teeth,
我认为联合国没有权力。
[speaker-05] so I've selected you as leader of the free world to receive this communi
所以我选你作为自由世界的领袖来接收这个信息
[speaker-05] And I invite you to begin negotiations in the largest-scale hostage situ
我邀请你们开始大规模人质事件的谈判。
[speaker-05] ation in history.
历史中的演变。
[speaker-05] A few weeks ago, an engineered virus was released,
几周前，一种人工制造的病毒被释放了。
[speaker-05] contained in all varieties of my product.
存在于我产品的所有版本中。
[speaker-05] Cannabis, cocaine, heroin, opium, ecstasy, and crystal meth.
大麻、可卡因、海洛因、鸦片、摇头丸和冰毒。
[speaker-05] Some of you are already infected, and this is what you can expect.
有些人已经被感染，这就是你们可能遇到的情况。
[speaker-05] In the coming days.
在接下来的几天里。
[speaker-05] After a brief incubation period,
经过一段短暂的潜伏期后，
[speaker-05] victims present with stage one symptoms.
受害者出现第一阶段症状。
[speaker-05] A blue rash.
蓝色皮疹。
[speaker-05] Next.
接下来。
[speaker-06] Second stage.
第二阶段。
[speaker-05] symptoms appear mania.
症状出现躁狂症状。
[speaker-05] As the virus enters the brain, very.
当病毒进入大脑时，情况会非常严重。
[speaker-05] Distressing to the victim and those around them.
对受害者及其周围人来说非常令人痛苦。
[speaker-05] Stage three.
第三阶段。
[speaker-05] Paralysis, muscles enter a state of catastrophic seizure,
瘫痪，肌肉出现严重的抽搐现象。
[speaker-05] and once the muscles of the thorax become affected.
当胸腔的肌肉受到影响时。
[speaker-05] Breathing becomes impossible,
呼吸变得不可能，
[speaker-05] leading to a very nasty death within twelve hours.
导致在十二小时内发生非常严重的死亡。
[speaker-05] I have good news to the millions.
有好消息要告诉数百万人。
[speaker-05] Already affected.
已经受到影响。
[speaker-05] It doesn't have to be this way.
不必如此。
[speaker-05] An antidote.
解毒剂。
[speaker-01] I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
对不起，对不起。
[speaker-06] I'm sorry.
对不起。
[speaker-01] What have you?
你有什么？
[speaker-02] done to me?
对我做了什么？
[speaker-03] You fucking bitch!
你这个该死的贱人！
[speaker-02] One hundred.
一百。
[speaker-05] percent effective and ready toship out worldwide at a moment's.
有效百分比高，随时可以全球发货。
[speaker-05] Notice, you have my word.
请注意，这是我的承诺。
[speaker-05] I will do this.
我会这么做。
[speaker-05] If the following conditions are met.
如果满足以下条件。
[speaker-05] Get out of my fucking room!
从我的房间里出去！
[speaker-05] First, you agree to end the war on drugs once and for all.
首先，您同意一劳永逸地结束毒品战争。
[speaker-05] All classes of substance are legalized.
所有物质类别均被合法化。
[speaker-05] Paving the way to a new marketplace in which sales are regulated.
为建立一个销售受监管的新市场铺平道路。
[speaker-05] And taxed as per alcohol.
按酒精税率征税。
[speaker-05] And second, my colleagues and I receive full legal immunity.
其次，我和我的同事们将获得完全的法律豁免权。
[speaker-05] Meet my terms,
查看我的条款。
[speaker-05] and I look forward to helping you keep our beloved country great.
我期待着帮助您维护我们亲爱的国家繁荣昌盛。
[speaker-05] Boosting our ailing economy and easing spending on law enforcement.
促进我们陷入困境的经济发展，并减少对执法部门的支出。
[speaker-05] Or continue this blinkered, outmoded, and frankly disastrous.
还是继续这种狭隘、过时且显然适得其反的做法吧。
[speaker-05] Exercise and prohibition.
锻炼与禁令。
[speaker-05] And live with blood on your hands.
并亲手创造繁荣。
[speaker-05] Save lives.
保护生命。
[speaker-05] Legalize.
合法化。
[speaker-02] I told you that shit was no good for you.
我告诉过你，那种做法对你没好处。
[speaker-05] Who is Poppy Adams?
波比·亚当斯是谁？
[speaker-05] After graduating Harvard Business School,
从哈佛商学院毕业后，
[speaker-05] Adams was briefly held for serious mental health issues.
亚当斯因严重的心理健康问题被短暂拘留。
[speaker-05] Before disappearing without a trace, intelligent.
在消失之前，非常聪明。
[speaker-04] Ambitious, ruthless, lacks empathy, superficial charm.
有野心、无情无义、缺乏同理心、表面上的魅力。
[speaker-04] All the elements of a great CEO.
优秀CEO的所有特质。
[speaker-04] Or psychopath.
或精神病患者。
[speaker-04] Following the broadcast of Adam's message to the president,
亚当向总统传达信息后，
[speaker-04] there were scenes of chaos today.
今天发生了混乱的场景。
[speaker-04] At medical centers across the country and around the world.
在全国各地的医疗中心以及世界各地。
[speaker-03] Cassidy, the blue rack.
卡西迪，蓝色架子。
[speaker-05] Rash is now being renamed the dancing disease as victims begin to exhibi
现在人们将皮疹重新称为“跳舞病”，因为受害者开始出现症状。
[speaker-05] t stage two symptoms.
第二阶段的症状。
[speaker-04] Let's prep the cryo unit.
让我们准备冷冻装置。
[speaker-03] You want to freeze him?
你想把他冷冻起来吗？
[speaker-02] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-06] Victims of the.
受害者们……
[speaker-04] virus caused by contaminated recreational drugs.
由受污染的娱乐药物引发的病毒。
[speaker-04] Flooded hospitals and clinics in fear for their lives.
医院和诊所里挤满了人，人们都担心自己的性命。
[speaker-08] Curfews and no.
宵禁时间及编号。
[speaker-05] No travel orders are being considered as authorities assess the scale of
正在评估事件规模时，尚未考虑任何旅行安排。
[speaker-05] the disaster.
灾难。
[speaker-05] Close it.
关闭它。
[speaker-06] But there has.
但是已经发生了。
[speaker-05] still been no official response from the president,
至今仍没有总统的官方回应。
[speaker-05] who remains locked in emergency talks.
谁仍坚持进行紧急谈判。
[speaker-03] Prepare a presidential decree.
准备一份总统法令。
[speaker-03] Tell intelligence and law enforcement to stand down.
请指示情报部门和执法部门停止行动。
[speaker-03] We're going to dance to this lady's tune.
我们将随着这位女士的节奏跳舞。
[speaker-03] We can make this work.
我们可以让这件事成功。
[speaker-05] we—we spin it that it's not a matter of negotiating with terrorists.
我们声称这不是与恐怖分子谈判的问题。
[speaker-05] What I'm proposing.
我提出的建议。
[speaker-03] Posing is we appear.
姿势就是我们的呈现方式。
[speaker-03] To agree to her demands to prevent global panic, and then.
为了满足她的要求以避免全球恐慌，然后……
[speaker-03] Let the junky scum go down.
让那些垃圾废物滚下吧。
[speaker-02] in flames.
处于火焰中。
[speaker-04] Huh.
哼。
[speaker-03] Yeah.
是的。
[speaker-02] Huh?
哼？
[speaker-02] Yeah.
是的。
[speaker-03] Take Poppy Adams and her so-called golden circle down with 'em.
带上波比·亚当斯和她所谓的“黄金圈”一起离开吧。
[speaker-03] No drug users.
没有吸毒者。
[speaker-03] No drug trade.
无毒品交易。
[speaker-03] It's a win-win situation here.
这是双赢的情况。
[speaker-05] But, sir, we're not talking about a handful of hostages.
但是，先生，我们说的可不是几名人质。
[speaker-05] We could be looking at the deaths of hundreds of millions worldwide.
全球可能会有数亿人因此丧生。
[speaker-05] Hundreds of millions of criminals—burdens to society.
数亿罪犯——是社会的负担。
[speaker-03] Am I right, Magoy?
对吗，马戈伊？
[speaker-03] Absolutely, sir.
当然，先生。
[speaker-03] But, sir, that's.
但是，先生，实际情况并非如此。
[speaker-05] What about people who are just experimenting?
那些只是进行实验的人呢？
[speaker-05] Folks who self-medicate.
自我治疗的患者。
[speaker-05] Functioning professionals.
职业人士。
[speaker-05] Kids, spare me the crap.
孩子们，别烦我了。
[speaker-03] The fact is, this presidency has just won a war on drugs.
事实上，这次总统任期在禁毒战争上取得了胜利。
[speaker-03] Congratulations, sir.
恭喜您，先生。
[speaker-02] Thank you.
谢谢。
[speaker-02] And that deserves a.
而且这值得肯定。
[speaker-03] A toast.
一杯酒。
[speaker-05] This is totally unethical, sir.
这完全是不道德的，先生。
[speaker-03] Fox, shut up.
狐狸，闭嘴。
[speaker-02] McCoy.
麦科伊。
[speaker-03] Declare martial law.
实施戒严令。
[speaker-03] We need to keep control, commandeer stadiums.
我们需要保持控制，征用体育场。
[speaker-03] Schools, cities.
学校，城市。
[speaker-02] Civic centers, order a press blackout,
市政中心，要求实施媒体禁令
[speaker-02] and put the military on standby to round these.
让军队保持待命状态以加强这些措施。
[speaker-02] Junkies up.
瘾君子增多了。
[speaker-01] Whether they broke.
他们是否破坏了。
[speaker-04] the law or not?
是法律吗？
[speaker-04] Those victims are human beings.
那些受害者都是人类。
[speaker-04] Tequila.
龙舌兰酒。
[speaker-04] He's a great guy.
他是个很棒的人。
[speaker-03] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-06] I'm a great agent.
我是个很棒的智能体。
[speaker-04] Right now, he's lying.
目前，他正在撒谎。
[speaker-06] And deep for you.
对你来说很深刻。
[speaker-04] Who ain't none our help?
谁不是我们的帮助呢？
[speaker-04] We can't make this personal, sir.
先生，我们无法将其视为个人内容。
[speaker-04] Personal, agent.
个人化，智能体。
[speaker-04] We can't stand by and let folks like him die.
我们不能坐视不管，让像他这样的人死去。
[speaker-04] These people were their only hope.
这些人是他们唯一的希望。
[speaker-03] We have to find that end.
我们必须找到那个终点。
[speaker-04] Pup's stockpiles.
狗的库存。
[speaker-04] Well, they could be anywhere.
嗯，它们可能出现在任何地方。
[speaker-04] She must have some on hand.
她肯定有一些在手。
[speaker-03] Locate poppy.
找到罂粟花。
[speaker-04] And obtain a sample for analysis.
获取一个样本用于分析。
[speaker-02] Maybe it can be replicated.
也许它可以被复制。
[speaker-05] Guys, but Charlie is on the phone with his girlfriend.
大家注意，查理正在和他的女朋友打电话。
[speaker-05] Looping you in now.
现在将您带入其中。
[speaker-05] Don't worry.
不用担心。
[speaker-05] I'm on a payphone, covered in.
我正在使用公用电话，周围一片混乱。
[speaker-05] Blue rash.
蓝色皮疹。
[speaker-05] Why didn't you tell me?
为什么不告诉我？
[speaker-05] All you said was, "Don't take any drugs.
你说的只是：“不要使用任何药物。”
[speaker-05] It was a music festival.
这是一场音乐节。
[speaker-05] For fuck's sake.
看在老天的份上。
[speaker-06] Shit.
该死。
[speaker-05] Shit.
[speaker-04] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-03] You need to get to the lab in Italy.
你需要前往意大利的实验室。
[speaker-02] Yes.
是的。
[speaker-05] Yes, I remember.
是的，我记得。
[speaker-03] Yeah, meet me there, and I'll give you the antidote.
好的，我在那里与你见面，我会给你解毒剂。
[speaker-06] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-04] All right, jet's ready.
好的，喷气机已经准备就绪。
[speaker-04] Whisky, Galahad.
威士忌，加拉哈德。
[speaker-04] Get to Italy.
前往意大利。
[speaker-03] You two need to fix this code name thing.
你们俩需要修复这个代码名问题。
[speaker-03] And with all due respect, sir,
恕我直言，先生，
[speaker-03] I don't think Galahad Senior is ready to return to field work.
我认为加拉哈德 Senior 还不适合返回现场工作。
[speaker-04] I did actually mean.
我确实是这个意思。
[speaker-04] Of course.
当然。
[speaker-02] And with all disrespect.
恕我直言，先生，
[speaker-02] I'm not going anywhere without him.
没有他，我哪儿也去不了。
[speaker-02] Brains, skills.
智慧，技能。
[speaker-02] Skipping rope.
跳绳。
[speaker-06] It's a laser.
这是一个激光设备。
[speaker-03] Whatever.
随便吧。
[speaker-02] Come on.
来吧。
[speaker-04] Haha.
哈哈。
[speaker-04] Go on.
来吧。
[speaker-04] Let's move.
让我们开始吧。
[speaker-03] Yes, sir.
是的，先生。
[speaker-01] I'm not sure.
我不太确定。
[speaker-03] Drink it.
喝下去吧。
[speaker-02] Wow.
哇。
[speaker-05] It's working already.
已经能用了。
[speaker-06] Thank God.
谢天谢地。
[speaker-05] Agent Whiskey, antidote confirmed at the target's location.
代理威士忌，在目标地点确认了解毒剂。
[speaker-05] Good luck.
祝你好运。
[speaker-03] We need you down here, Galahad, to secure the control room.
我们需要你在这里，加拉哈德，去保护控制室。
[speaker-02] Probably a good idea, Harry.
也许这是个好主意，哈里。
[speaker-02] Call you from the top, yeah.
从上面打电话给你，没错。
[speaker-04] Buongiorno.
早上好。
[speaker-02] I'm here for a news briefing.
我在这里参加一个新闻发布会。
[speaker-03] An inspection of the implants.
对植入物的检查。
[speaker-02] Document for courtesy?
是提供文档以表示礼貌吗？
[speaker-02] Certainly.
当然。
[speaker-03] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-08] I'm not a killer.
我不是杀手。
[speaker-02] What the hell is this thing?
这到底是什么东西？
[speaker-02] Hey, what the fuck is he doing?
嘿，他到底在干什么？
[speaker-02] I'm so sorry about this.
非常抱歉这件事。
[speaker-03] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-06] At the controls.
掌控一切。
[speaker-03] Trols in position.
控制杆处于正确位置。
[speaker-08] I'm not afraid to die.
我不怕死。
[speaker-04] I'm not a man.
我不是男人。
[speaker-02] Keep this cable car here till we get back.
把这缆车留在这里，等我们回来再处理。
[speaker-02] Roger that, Exie.
明白，Exie。
[speaker-03] Claire's death.
克莱尔的死亡。
[speaker-02] Definitely here.
肯定在这里。
[speaker-02] We're getting warmer.
天气越来越暖和了。
[speaker-08] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-02] Harry Hart.
哈里·哈特。
[speaker-02] Harry Hart's.
哈里·哈特的。
[speaker-06] Super spy.
超级间谍。
[speaker-02] Looks like we've got a door.
看起来我们有一扇门。
[speaker-02] Yep.
是的。
[speaker-04] There you go.
就是这样。
[speaker-06] I'll cover.
我会处理。
[speaker-03] Hi there.
嗨，你好。
[speaker-02] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-06] Sorry, I'm late.
抱歉，我迟到了。
[speaker-02] You guys did not make this place easy to find.
你们让这个地方很难找到。
[speaker-02] Who are you?
你是谁？
[speaker-02] I'm here to collect this antidote.
我来这里是为了取走这种解药。
[speaker-03] For Singapore.
对于新加坡。
[speaker-02] Yeah.
是的。
[speaker-06] You.
你。
[speaker-03] Are you thinking?
你在思考吗？
[speaker-04] Are you paying?
你在支付吗？
[speaker-02] Yes.
是的。
[speaker-06] Hey, how are you still alive?
嘿，你怎么还活着？
[speaker-03] River.
河流。
[speaker-05] What are you doing here, River?
你在这里做什么，河流？
[speaker-03] Hi, Clara.
嗨，克拉拉。
[speaker-02] Sarah, what happens at Glasgow stays at Glasgow.
莎拉，在格拉斯哥发生的事件仍留在格拉斯哥。
[speaker-03] You motherfucker!
你这个混蛋！
[speaker-03] Bye, Charlie.
再见，查理。
[speaker-02] Sound the alarm!
发出警报！
[speaker-06] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-01] You fucking cocker.
你这个该死的混蛋。
[speaker-03] Cockroaches!
蟑螂！
[speaker-03] Jam the door!
敲敲门！
[speaker-05] Boss.
老板。
[speaker-08] Gather head.
聚拢起来。
[speaker-03] We're coming.
我们来了。
[speaker-03] All clear at the bottom.
底部一切正常。
[speaker-03] Galahad, come in.
加勒哈德，进来吧。
[speaker-03] Open the fucking door!
打开该死的门！
[speaker-03] Is it blocked?
被堵住了吗？
[speaker-03] Open the door!
打开门！
[speaker-03] Harry, come on, Marine.
哈里，快点，海军陆战队员。
[speaker-02] A ray butterfly.
光线蝴蝶。
[speaker-02] No, Harry, you've got to shut the doors, please.
不，哈里，请你把门关上。
[speaker-02] Come on, we've got to go now, please.
快点，我们现在必须走了，拜托了。
[speaker-02] Shut the fucking door, Harry.
把该死的门关上，哈里。
[speaker-03] are you?
你是吗？
[speaker-06] dead?
死了吗？
[speaker-02] Well done, Harry.
干得好，哈里。
[speaker-02] Come on.
快点。
[speaker-06] On now.
现在开始。
[speaker-03] No.
不。
[speaker-08] Hey, stop.
嘿，停一下。
[speaker-03] Thanks.
谢谢。
[speaker-01] You all get down there.
你们都到那边去。
[speaker-02] All clear.
一切正常。
[speaker-02] Hello, Eggsy.
嘿， Eggsy。
[speaker-02] Enjoy the ride, bruv.
享受这段旅程吧，兄弟。
[speaker-03] I'm sorry.
对不起。
[speaker-08] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-08] Shit!
糟了！
[speaker-08] Ah.
啊。
[speaker-08] Ah!
啊！
[speaker-08] The.
那个。
[speaker-03] All the buttons are dead.
所有按钮都坏了。
[speaker-03] Control's gone.
控制已失效。
[speaker-03] Everything's in shutdown.
一切都处于关闭状态。
[speaker-03] You're on your own, Eggsy.
你得自己了，埃格斯。
[speaker-06] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-08] Ah!
啊！
[speaker-08] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-04] Ah!
啊！
[speaker-08] Oh, God!
哦，天哪！
[speaker-08] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-01] I'm not a man.
我不是男人。
[speaker-08] The world is a dangerous place, but I'm not scared of anything.
世界是个危险的地方，但我什么都不怕。
[speaker-08] Oh!
啊！
[speaker-08] I'm not a bad person.
我不是个坏人。
[speaker-08] What the fuck is that?
那到底是什么鬼东西？
[speaker-03] Oh my God.
哦，我的天啊。
[speaker-06] Oh.
啊。
[speaker-08] Oh!
啊！
[speaker-03] Huh.
哼。
[speaker-08] Oh.
啊。
[speaker-08] No.
不。
[speaker-08] Hmm.
嗯。
[speaker-03] You've got to be fucking kidding!
你一定在开玩笑吧！
[speaker-08] Oh.
啊。
[speaker-08] Ah!
啊！
[speaker-08] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-08] I'm sorry.
对不起。
[speaker-08] Whoa!
哇！
[speaker-08] The.
那个。
[speaker-08] Jesus!
天啊！
[speaker-03] What the hell is that?
那到底是什么东西？
[speaker-06] Shit.
真糟糕。
[speaker-08] I can't.
我做不到。
[speaker-08] Ah!
啊！
[speaker-08] Ah.
啊。
[speaker-01] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-08] Oh.
[speaker-08] We're going to get it!
我们一定会得到它！
[speaker-06] Huh?
哼？
[speaker-04] That's the first decent shit I've had in three weeks.
这是三周来我遇到的第一件还算不错的东西。
[speaker-02] Harry, meet us at the emergency rendezvous point.
哈里，请在紧急集合点与我们会合。
[speaker-02] Roger that.
明白。
[speaker-06] Got you on the GPS.
已通过 GPS 定位到你。
[speaker-03] Yes.
是的。
[speaker-06] So weird to think.
真奇怪，令人难以置信。
[speaker-02] This tiny thing could save the world.
这个小东西或许能拯救世界。
[speaker-04] Let me have a look.
让我看看吧。
[speaker-02] Harry.
哈里。
[speaker-02] Am I late?
我迟到了吗？
[speaker-06] You found the antidote.
你找到了解药。
[speaker-06] Fucking dickhead!
该死的混蛋！
[speaker-03] I just saved your life.
我刚刚救了你的命。
[speaker-03] Yeah, and cost millions of peopleless.
是的，它让数百万人付出了代价。
[speaker-06] I'm sorry.
对不起。
[speaker-04] All right, they're going for cover and reloading.
好的，他们正在寻找掩护并重新装弹。
[speaker-04] I'll fix their wagons.
我会修理他们的马车。
[speaker-04] Cover me, boys.
伙计们，掩护我吧。
[speaker-06] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-01] Wait.
等待。
[speaker-03] Exactly.
完全正确。
[speaker-03] The other side.
另一方。
[speaker-06] What the fuck is wrong with you?
你到底怎么了？
[speaker-02] You're having a brain fart.
你刚才犯了个大错误。
[speaker-03] Does that look like he's working with?
看起来他好像正在工作吗？
[speaker-02] them.
它们。
[speaker-06] Harry.
哈里。
[speaker-02] Are you seeing butterflies?
你看到蝴蝶了吗？
[speaker-04] I know what I'm seeing.
我知道自己看到了什么。
[speaker-03] Same.
相同。
[speaker-08] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-06] Ah.
啊。
[speaker-02] Good job.
好工作。
[speaker-02] We didn't need our help.
我们不需要他们的帮助。
[speaker-03] Thank fucking Krass.
谢谢该死的Krass。
[speaker-03] I didn't need any backup.
我不需要任何备份。
[speaker-03] I'm out of ammo.
我的弹药用完了。
[speaker-03] Troop carrier coming in.
部队运输车正在进入。
[speaker-03] What have you got?
你有什么吗？
[speaker-04] Fuck.
该死。
[speaker-06] There's a fuck ton.
有大量的东西。
[speaker-02] ton of them.
大量的它们。
[speaker-08] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-03] What is this?
这是什么？
[speaker-04] Looks like you packed for.
看起来你已经准备好了行李。
[speaker-03] a fucking slumber party, not a mission.
一个该死的睡眠派对，不是任务。
[speaker-02] And they've got fucking Gatling guns.
他们还有该死的加特林机枪。
[speaker-03] You have ten seconds to surrender before we open fire.
你只有十秒时间投降，否则我们就开火了。
[speaker-02] Guys, hurry up!
大家快一点！
[speaker-03] Ten.
十。
[speaker-03] Hey.
嘿。
[speaker-03] Butterfly guy.
蝴蝶人。
[speaker-06] You don't look like.
你看起来并不像那样。
[speaker-04] ginger fixed you, right?
ginger 固定了你，对吧？
[speaker-03] I said, I'm empty.
我说，我空着呢。
[speaker-03] Give me yours.
给我你的那个。
[speaker-04] Five, Harry.
五，哈里。
[speaker-03] Give him the fucking gun.
把那该死的枪给他。
[speaker-03] Hurry now!
快一点！
[speaker-08] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-06] Oh, fuck it.
哦，算了吧。
[speaker-03] Hire Harry.
雇用哈里。
[speaker-03] Get down!
趴下！
[speaker-08] Get out of here!
离开这里！
[speaker-01] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-03] Honestly, I.
老实说，我。
[speaker-06] Gary, what the fuck?
加里，搞什么鬼？
[speaker-03] What is wrong with you?
你怎么了？
[speaker-03] Ran the file on purpose.
故意运行了那个文件。
[speaker-03] You're a fucking idiot!
你真是个白痴！
[speaker-03] You're out of control, Harry.
你已经失控了，哈里。
[speaker-03] If we made it out of here, it was going to kill us both.
如果我们离开这里，会害死我们俩。
[speaker-03] For fuck's sake!
看在老天的份上！
[speaker-03] He looks like he wouldn't have fucking acted.
他看起来根本不会做出那种事。
[speaker-03] Oh, ye of little faith!
哦，你们这些没信心的人！
[speaker-03] This does not mean you are off the fucking hook.
这并不意味着你就可以摆脱责任。
[speaker-04] We need to go dark.
我们需要保持沉默。
[speaker-06] We don't know who else.
我们不知道还有谁。
[speaker-04] Statesmen could be working against us.
政治家们可能正在与我们作对。
[speaker-02] This is all my fault.
这都是我的错。
[speaker-02] You weren't ready for the field, and I pushed for it.
你还没准备好进入战场，而我却强行推进了。
[speaker-04] hand.
手。
[speaker-04] You think you'd have let us live?
你认为你会让我们活下去吗？
[speaker-04] You should be thanking me for saving our asses.
你应该感谢我救了我们的命。
[speaker-03] Try saying that to fucking whiskey.
试着用那该死的威士忌来表达这句话。
[speaker-02] You are.
你存在。
[speaker-06] Unbelievable.
难以置信。
[speaker-03] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-02] Merlin, can you hear me?
梅林，你能听到我说话吗？
[speaker-02] Whisky's done.
威士忌已经准备好了。
[speaker-04] He's been shot.
他被枪击了。
[speaker-04] What happened?
发生了什么？
[speaker-02] He got caught in the crossfire.
他被交火波及了。
[speaker-04] I've applied the alpha gel.
我已经涂了Alpha凝胶。
[speaker-02] Joe, we'll bring him in.
乔，我们把他带进来吧。
[speaker-02] I've got to find a way to get back up to that lab and retrieve more anti
我得想办法回到实验室，取回更多的抗药剂。
[speaker-02] dote.
[speaker-05] Charlie, what's happening?
查理，发生了什么？
[speaker-05] Where are you?
你在哪里？
[speaker-04] Everything's under control.
一切都在掌控之中。
[speaker-04] I'm sorry, Charlie.
对不起，查理。
[speaker-05] I'm so sorry.
非常抱歉。
[speaker-05] Please don't tell Poppy it was me.
请不要告诉波比是我在做这件事。
[speaker-05] They followed.
他们跟了上去。
[speaker-02] Don't worry, darling.
别担心，亲爱的。
[speaker-06] What happens in Italy?
在意大利发生了什么？
[speaker-06] Place in Italy.
在意大利的地点。
[speaker-05] Thank you.
谢谢。
[speaker-02] Merlin, change your plans.
梅林，改变你的计划。
[speaker-02] Wu Ting Feng, Singapore.
吴廷峰，新加坡。
[speaker-02] Exactly.
完全正确。
[speaker-02] It's the only lead we've got.
这是我们目前唯一的线索。
[speaker-04] So I suggest you find out who he is.
所以我建议你查明他是谁。
[speaker-04] Come on.
来吧。
[speaker-06] I'm not sure if I can trust you.
我不确定是否可以信任你。
[speaker-05] Wu Tingfeng.
吴廷峰。
[speaker-05] He's an assistant at a law firm.
他是一家律师事务所的助理。
[speaker-04] Let's get through that firewall.
让我们通过那道防火墙吧。
[speaker-04] Yep.
是的。
[speaker-05] Marlon.
马伦。
[speaker-05] If you ever wanted to do more than this.
如果你曾经想要做更多事情。
[speaker-04] Are you serious?
你是认真的吗？
[speaker-04] Yeah, this is vital.
是的，这非常重要。
[speaker-04] Without us, they'd be lost.
没有我们，他们就会迷失方向。
[speaker-05] I know, but you know what I mean.
我知道，但你们明白我的意思。
[speaker-05] Get out there in the field.
到现场去吧。
[speaker-04] Well, have you ever asked?
那么，你曾经问过吗？
[speaker-04] Of course, I have.
当然，我有。
[speaker-05] But every time an agent's position has come up, whiskey.
但每次出现代理的位置时，都是威士忌。
[speaker-05] Has voted against me?
是否投票反对我？
[speaker-04] Yeah.
是的。
[speaker-05] Look.
看。
[speaker-05] Check it out.
看看吧。
[speaker-05] Email in from Poppy, from a senior partner at the firm.
来自公司高级合伙人的邮件，由Poppy发送。
[speaker-04] Their coordinates.
他们的坐标。
[speaker-01] Cambodia.
柬埔寨。
[speaker-04] You.
你。
[speaker-04] You have any reconnaissance drones down in Asia?
你在亚洲有侦察无人机吗？
[speaker-05] Sending him in right now.
现在就派他去。
[speaker-06] I'm not sure if I can do this.
我不确定是否能做到这一点。
[speaker-05] The government today urged.
政府今天呼吁。
[speaker-04] Golden Circle victims to report to the temporary field hospitals now set
金环地区的受害者现在应前往临时野战医院报告情况
[speaker-04] up across the country.
遍布全国各地。
[speaker-04] The president's handling of the crisis has been commended by other world
总统对危机的处理方式得到了其他国家的赞赏
[speaker-03] Damn, politics never been.
该死，我从来不懂政治。
[speaker-02] so easy.
太容易了。
[speaker-02] Oh, Jesus, Fox!
哦，天哪，狐狸！
[speaker-02] What?
什么？
[speaker-06] Sure that any antidote.
当然，有任何解药。
[speaker-06] Oh God.
哦，天哪。
[speaker-04] Like I said, sir, Mr.
就像我说的，先生，先生。
[speaker-05] Affects all people from all backgrounds.
影响所有背景的人。
[speaker-05] I'm disappointed.
我很失望。
[speaker-02] Disappointed and disgusted.
感到失望且厌恶。
[speaker-02] President.
总统。
[speaker-06] I routinely.
我经常这样做。
[speaker-02] Work a twenty-hour.
工作时间为二十小时。
[speaker-04] day for you, seven days a week.
对你来说是一天，每周七天。
[speaker-04] Maybe some can do that without chemical help.
也许有些人可以在没有化学辅助的情况下做到这一点。
[speaker-04] Countless people are going to die.
无数人将死去。
[speaker-04] You can save them, sir.
先生，您可以保存它们。
[speaker-04] Innocent people like me.
像我这样的无辜人。
[speaker-02] Not that innocent.
并非如此无辜。
[speaker-08] Oh!
哦！
[speaker-08] I'm gonna make you mine.
我会让你属于我。
[speaker-08] I'm not a hero.
我不是英雄。
[speaker-05] He looks great.
他看起来很棒。
[speaker-05] Good.
好的。
[speaker-03] Good news, gentlemen.
好消息，先生们。
[speaker-06] He'll be back on his feet.
他会重新站起来。
[speaker-02] I'm not certain that's a good idea.
我不确定那是个好主意。
[speaker-02] What do you mean?
你是什么意思？
[speaker-02] I shot Agent Whisky deliberately.
我故意射杀了Whisky代理。
[speaker-02] He was working against us, and until we find out why,
他一直在与我们作对，在我们查明原因之前，他将继续如此。
[speaker-02] I say we trust no one.
我说我们不应该信任任何人。
[speaker-02] Harry's sick.
哈里生病了。
[speaker-04] This whole thing is my fault.
这一切都是我的错。
[speaker-02] I thought he was ready.
我以为他已经准备好了。
[speaker-04] I'm sorry.
很抱歉。
[speaker-02] to take this.
拿这个。
[speaker-02] Listen to me.
听我说。
[speaker-02] This is not about my mental health.
这与我的心理健康无关。
[speaker-02] If there's a chance, there's a double agent in our midst.
如果有机会，那说明我们中间就有个间谍。
[speaker-02] Was.
是。
[speaker-02] The statesman himself has a dark agenda.
这位政治家本身有着不可告人的目的。
[speaker-02] We have to safeguard this mission.
我们必须保护这一任务。
[speaker-02] We both know the president wants these victims dead.
我们俩都知道总统希望这些受害者死掉。
[speaker-02] Hey, baby.
嘿，宝贝。
[speaker-06] Look, Harry.
看，哈里。
[speaker-06] I trust you.
我相信你。
[speaker-04] I always have, but it's about this.
我一直都是这样，但这是关于这件事的。
[speaker-06] situation.
情况。
[speaker-04] We need statesmen's resources,
我们需要政治家所需的资源。
[speaker-04] and I need to know that you are fit for work.
我需要确认你能够胜任工作。
[speaker-04] Why didn't you call me?
为什么你不打电话给我？
[speaker-04] Are you the banana man?
你是香蕉人吗？
[speaker-05] Listen, we're on the verge of.
听着，我们即将开始。
[speaker-04] finding an antidote.
寻找解药。
[speaker-03] Actually, though, it's going to be.
实际上，不过，事情将会如此。
[speaker-04] It'll be all right.
一切都会好的。
[speaker-02] Look left for me.
帮我看左边。
[speaker-02] There's nothing wrong with my brain.
我的大脑没有问题。
[speaker-02] Look right.
看向右边。
[speaker-04] Can you remember the headline when you uncovered that spying at the Pent
当你揭露那次间谍行为时，你能想起标题吗
[speaker-04] Difficult.
困难。
[speaker-02] England beat Germany five one.
英格兰队以5比1击败德国队。
[speaker-02] Thatcher's assassination at.
撒切尔被暗杀的事件。
[speaker-04] Charles and Dwight.
查尔斯和德怀特。
[speaker-02] Hey, Bjorn.
嘿，比约恩。
[speaker-04] Babe, if you can hear me.
宝贝，如果你能听到我说话。
[speaker-04] I want you to know that I love you.
我想让你知道，我爱你。
[speaker-04] If we get through this, and you'll have me back, I want to.
如果我们能成功完成这件事，而你又让我回来，我就想要。
[speaker-06] be with you, no matter what.
无论发生什么，我都会陪在你身边。
[speaker-04] I promise I won't let you down.
我保证不会让你失望。
[speaker-04] It's all gonna be all right.
一切都会好起来的。
[speaker-04] My favorite singer.
我最喜欢的歌手。
[speaker-02] I don't bloody know how, but I know that.
我真不知道该怎么做，但我知道该怎么做。
[speaker-04] It's John Denver.
是约翰·丹佛的歌。
[speaker-04] Marlene.
玛琳。
[speaker-06] Have you got eyes on that location?
你有没有注意那个地点？
[speaker-03] Yet.
然而。
[speaker-06] Soon, the reconnaissance.
很快，侦察任务就会开始。
[speaker-04] Jonathan's drone's about an hour away, which gives us time to sort out.
乔纳森的无人机大约在一小时车程外，这让我们有时间处理其他事情。
[speaker-03] No time for anything.
没有时间做任何事情。
[speaker-03] I'm leaving now, with or without you.
我现在就出发，不管你有在还是没有我。
[speaker-01] The.
那个。
[speaker-08] I'm not a good person.
我不是个好人。
[speaker-08] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-02] Hello.
你好。
[speaker-04] Identify yourself.
请介绍自己。
[speaker-04] My name is Stacy.
我的名字是斯泰西。
[speaker-02] Stacey Pruitt, Miss Poppy Adams' attorney.
斯泰西·普鲁伊特，波比·亚当斯小姐的律师。
[speaker-04] Papa, you expecting a lawyer tonight?
爸爸，你今晚要请律师吗？
[speaker-06] Please send them in.
请把他们送进来。
[speaker-05] But don't forget to.
但别忘了。
[speaker-05] Reactivate the landmines.
重新激活地雷。
[speaker-06] Good evening.
晚上好。
[speaker-04] Miss Adams, my lawyer.
亚当斯小姐，我的律师。
[speaker-06] Is bringing you the document right now.
正在立即将文件送给您。
[speaker-06] Hurry up!
快一点！
[speaker-06] And once you countersign, it becomes an executive decree,
一旦您签字确认，它就成为一项行政法令了。
[speaker-06] and you can't back out.
而且你无法退步。
[speaker-06] And then I release the antidote.
然后我会释放解毒剂。
[speaker-04] Can you give me any assurance?
你能给我一些保证吗？
[speaker-04] You can get it out there in time.
您可以在适当的时候拿到它。
[speaker-04] Where's it going to come from?
它将从哪里来？
[speaker-04] How long it'll take to distribute?
分发需要多长时间？
[speaker-04] I wouldn't worry about that.
我不必担心那个。
[speaker-05] I have secure stockpiles hidden in every major city worldwide.
我在全球每个主要城市都藏有安全的库存。
[speaker-05] And when I enter the access code,
当我输入访问代码时，
[speaker-05] my fleet of drones will distribute the antidote immediately.
我的无人机舰队将立即分发解毒剂。
[speaker-05] So, don't dilly-dally signing that document, 'cause time is running out.
所以，别再犹豫不决地签署那份文件了，因为时间已经不多了。
[speaker-01] I'm not.
我并非如此。
[speaker-02] You.
你。
[speaker-01] Dumb.
愚蠢。
[speaker-06] Beds.
床铺。
[speaker-02] You all right?
你没事吧？
[speaker-02] What was that phone call you got?
你接到的那个电话是什么？
[speaker-04] Let's not hurry.
我们不必着急。
[speaker-06] I don't think you sympathise.
我认为你并不同情。
[speaker-04] And I'm not really.
我其实并不是那样。
[speaker-06] in the mood for a.
有心情做……
[speaker-04] A lecture.
讲座。
[speaker-02] All right.
好的。
[speaker-02] How about a martini?
来杯马提尼怎么样？
[speaker-02] For old times' sake.
为了旧日的缘故。
[speaker-06] You know what.
你知道的。
[speaker-04] I had a girlfriend.
我有一个女朋友。
[speaker-04] Roster.
名单。
[speaker-04] And it broke me.
它让我崩溃了。
[speaker-04] Now, if this mission fails.
现在，如果这项任务失败了怎么办？
[speaker-04] She's gonna die.
她要死了。
[speaker-04] I know it's against Kingsman rules, having a relationship.
我知道这与Kingsman的规则相冲突，因为存在恋爱关系。
[speaker-02] When I was shot.
当我被枪击时。
[speaker-02] Can you guess what the last thing was that flashed through my mind?
你能猜到最后闪过脑海的那个词是什么吗？
[speaker-02] It was absolutely.
确实如此。
[speaker-02] Nothing.
无。
[speaker-02] I had no ties.
我没有任何关系。
[speaker-02] No bittersweet memories.
没有苦乐参半的回忆。
[speaker-02] I was leaving nothing behind.
我没有留下任何东西。
[speaker-02] Never experienced companionship.
从未体验过亲密关系。
[speaker-02] Never been in love.
从未恋爱过。
[speaker-02] At that moment.
在那一刻。
[speaker-02] All I felt.
我所感受到的一切。
[speaker-02] It's loneliness.
这就是孤独。
[speaker-02] Regret.
遗憾。
[speaker-04] I'm sorry.
对不起。
[speaker-02] Don't be.
不要这样。
[speaker-02] Just know that having something to lose.
只需知道有东西可以失去。
[speaker-02] It's what makes life worth living.
这就是让生活值得活下去的原因。
[speaker-02] Let's go and see if you'll go.
让我们去看看你是否会去。
[speaker-04] Missed you, right?
想念你，对吧？
[speaker-04] Gentlemen.
先生们。
[speaker-04] I hate to break up a party.
我讨厌破坏派对的气氛。
[speaker-04] We're nearly there.
我们快到了。
[speaker-04] So I suggest we get ready.
所以我建议我们准备一下。
[speaker-04] Follow me.
跟我来。
[speaker-02] Oh, yeah.
哦，对啊。
[speaker-06] Yes.
是的。
[speaker-01] I'm sorry.
对不起。
[speaker-01] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-04] Hello, gorgeous.
你好，真美。
[speaker-04] What's your name?
您叫什么名字？
[speaker-04] How would you like to ride home on a real cowboy?
你想如何骑着真正的牛仔回家呢？
[speaker-04] I got a six-pack of cold ones all night, so my roomies out all night.
我整晚都喝到了一箱冰啤酒，所以我的伙伴们也整晚都在喝酒。
[speaker-04] You can scream my name as loud as you need to, sugar.
你可以尽情大声喊出我的名字，亲爱的。
[speaker-05] To do this to you, Jack.
为了让你能这么做，杰克。
[speaker-04] Who's this pretty lady?
这个美丽的女士是谁？
[speaker-04] She's dead.
她已经死了。
[speaker-05] Cops said, "Wrong place, wrong time.
警察说：“错地方，错时间。”
[speaker-05] " Hey, honey.
“嘿，亲爱的。”
[speaker-06] I'm heading to the grocery store.
我正要去杂货店。
[speaker-08] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-01] Hi, name.
嗨，名字。
[speaker-08] See Adam.
参见亚当。
[speaker-06] I'm not sure.
我不太确定。
[speaker-08] I'm not a bad person.
我不是个坏人。
[speaker-05] Ginger.
姜黄。
[speaker-04] That damn butterfly guy shot me in the fucking head.
那个讨厌的蝴蝶人朝我的头开枪了。
[speaker-05] Why would he do that?
他为什么要那样做？
[speaker-04] Well, I'm guessing you didn't fix him right.
嗯，我猜你没把他修好。
[speaker-04] Where the hell is he?
他到底在哪儿？
[speaker-05] He's on his way to Cambodia, with Eggsy and Merlin.
他和埃格斯、梅林一起正在前往柬埔寨的路上。
[speaker-05] That's where Poppy's base is.
那是波比的基地所在之处。
[speaker-04] Eggsy's gonna need backup.
埃格斯需要支援。
[speaker-05] Get the silver pony.
获取那匹银色小马。
[speaker-04] A pony on the runway, and ready to take off.
跑道上有一匹小马，准备起飞。
[speaker-06] Hey, looking good.
嘿，看起来不错。
[speaker-03] Merlin.
梅林。
[speaker-06] Feeling good, Eggsy.
感觉不错，埃格斯。
[speaker-04] Haha.
哈哈。
[speaker-04] Right.
好的。
[speaker-04] This is yours.
这是你的。
[speaker-04] That's for you.
那是给你的。
[speaker-04] Press thes.
按这些。
[speaker-04] Minesweeper.
扫雷游戏。
[speaker-04] Courtesy of statesmen.
由政治家们提供。
[speaker-04] More about these.
关于这些的更多内容。
[speaker-04] those are hand grenades.
那些是手榴弹。
[speaker-04] As discussed, this is for the end game.
如所讨论的，这是针对最终游戏的内容。
[speaker-04] I'm entrusting it to you.
我将其交给你处理。
[speaker-04] And I'm entrusting this.
我也将此任务交给你处理。
[speaker-04] To me.
对我来说。
[speaker-01] I'm not a man.
我不是男人。
[speaker-08] The.
[speaker-03] Millions of Golden Circle victims worldwide.
全球有数百万“金环组织”受害者。
[speaker-03] Are now entering stage three paralysis.
现在正进入第三阶段的瘫痪状态。
[speaker-03] In his latest statement, the president promised he was.
在他最新的声明中，总统承诺自己确实是男性。
[speaker-05] doing everything in his power to speed up negotiations and save lives.
尽一切努力加快谈判进程并挽救生命。
[speaker-05] But fears are growing that, for many, it may soon be too late.
但人们越来越担心，对许多人来说，可能很快就会为时已晚。
[speaker-05] Our thoughts and prayers are with the victims.
我们的思念与祈祷与受害者们同在。
[speaker-05] God help us all.
愿上帝保佑我们所有人。
[speaker-08] Pinch the movement.
挤压动作。
[speaker-06] We're in position.
我们已就位。
[speaker-06] Don't move.
不要移动。
[speaker-04] You move.
你移动了。
[speaker-04] We die.
我们死了。
[speaker-04] Luckily, I have this.
幸运的是，我有这个。
[speaker-04] This spray will freeze the trigger mechanism.
这种喷雾可以冻结触发机制。
[speaker-04] Give us a split second.
给我们一瞬间时间。
[speaker-04] So, on the count of three.
那么，数到三。
[speaker-04] I want you to, Mal.
我想让你这么做，马尔。
[speaker-06] Our journey together.
我们共同的旅程。
[speaker-04] began many years ago.
多年前就开始了。
[speaker-04] And your father—it's the same thing for us.
你的父亲——对我们来说也是一样。
[speaker-02] Our journey began with a mistake.
我们的旅程始于一个错误。
[speaker-04] I made.
我做了。
[speaker-06] Give me the count.
请告诉我数量。
[speaker-06] That's not it.
不是那样。
[speaker-04] It's empty.
为空。
[speaker-04] Split seconds over.
时间已分割完毕。
[speaker-04] You two need to get going.
你们俩得赶紧开始吧。
[speaker-04] The scorpion—he's right.
蝎子——他说得对。
[speaker-04] Mission comes first.
任务优先。
[speaker-06] I'm not too comfortable.
我不太舒服。
[speaker-06] This is toxic.
这是有毒的。
[speaker-04] There's no time for emotion, or maybe our training.
没有时间表达情感，或许也没有时间进行训练。
[speaker-04] Or we all die.
或者我们都会死去。
[speaker-04] Now, get on with it.
现在，就开始吧。
[speaker-04] Do as you're told.
按照指示行事。
[speaker-04] Move it.
开始行动吧。
[speaker-04] Go.
开始吧。
[speaker-06] It's been an honor.
这是一种荣幸。
[speaker-06] Good luck.
祝你好运。
[speaker-06] Heaven.
天堂。
[speaker-04] West Virginia.
西弗吉尼亚州。
[speaker-06] Blue Ridge Mountain.
蓝岭山脉。
[speaker-04] Mount Shannondore River.
香农多尔山河。
[speaker-03] Poppy, come in.
波比，进来吧。
[speaker-06] Life is all.
生活就是如此。
[speaker-04] Are you expecting another lawyer?
你还在期待另一位律师吗？
[speaker-06] a guy here.
这里有个男人。
[speaker-04] Singing.
唱歌。
[speaker-06] Singing.
[speaker-04] A breeze, country road.
微风，乡村道路。
[speaker-04] Take me home.
带我回家。
[speaker-04] To the place.
到那个地方。
[speaker-04] I belong.
我属于这里。
[speaker-06] West Virginia.
西弗吉尼亚州。
[speaker-04] Young.
年轻。
[speaker-04] Mountain mama.
山中的妈妈。
[speaker-01] Take me.
带我走吧。
[speaker-04] home.
家。
[speaker-04] Country roads.
国家道路。
[speaker-04] Poppy, we got a situation.
波比，我们遇到了麻烦。
[speaker-03] Country road.
国家道路。
[speaker-04] Go.
去吧。
[speaker-04] Take me home.
带我回家。
[speaker-04] To the place.
到那个地方。
[speaker-04] Place I belong.
我属于这个地方。
[speaker-04] West Virginia.
西弗吉尼亚州。
[speaker-04] Mountain Mama.
山中的妈妈。
[speaker-04] Take me home.
带我回家。
[speaker-04] Country road.
国家公路。
[speaker-01] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-08] Oh.
[speaker-05] He stepped on a landmine.
他踩到了地雷。
[speaker-06] Can we get somebody?
我们能找个人吗？
[speaker-05] out there to clean that up.
在外部进行清理工作。
[speaker-05] Hello.
你好。
[speaker-01] I'm not sure.
我不确定。
[speaker-06] We're under attack.
我们正在受到攻击。
[speaker-05] Code five.
五点。
[speaker-06] You two, off your fucking ass!
你们俩，赶紧起来！
[speaker-03] guard the door.
守门。
[speaker-03] Sir Elton, stay here.
埃尔顿先生，留在这里。
[speaker-03] We're under attack.
我们正在受到攻击。
[speaker-01] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-06] Is it a rescue attempt?
这是一次救援尝试吗？
[speaker-03] Might be.
可能是。
[speaker-06] Yes.
是的。
[speaker-01] Wednesday.
星期三。
[speaker-01] night's alright.
夜晚也没问题。
[speaker-01] Hey.
嘿。
[speaker-03] Isn't that supposed to be Saturday?
这不是应该是在星期六吗？
[speaker-03] What day is it today?
今天是星期几？
[speaker-03] Exactly.
完全正确。
[speaker-06] Ah!
啊！
[speaker-04] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-08] Ah!
啊！
[speaker-03] Elton, just calm down.
埃尔顿，冷静点吧。
[speaker-03] Fuck you.
去你的。
[speaker-06] Huh.
哼。
[speaker-08] Oh my!
哦，我的天！
[speaker-08] Oh, God!
哦，天哪！
[speaker-03] Stay there, Elton.
待在那儿，埃尔顿。
[speaker-03] Fuck off!
去你的！
[speaker-03] Or I'll fuck you up.
或者我会搞砸你的事情。
[speaker-01] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-08] Ah!
啊！
[speaker-01] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-08] Ah!
啊！
[speaker-08] Get over there!
去那边吧！
[speaker-08] Come on, man.
来吧，兄弟。
[speaker-03] Fuck me.
靠。
[speaker-03] Ah!
啊！
[speaker-08] Oh!
[speaker-01] Ah.
啊。
[speaker-08] Ah.
[speaker-01] Ah!
啊！
[speaker-08] Ah!
[speaker-01] Ah.
啊。
[speaker-06] Wow.
哇。
[speaker-08] Oh!
哦！
[speaker-01] Whoa.
哇。
[speaker-08] Holy cow!
天哪！
[speaker-05] Get this out of here!
把这个从这里拿走！
[speaker-05] Go.
去吧。
[speaker-06] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-01] Get the keys.
把钥匙拿过来。
[speaker-06] Get the case.
把箱子拿过来。
[speaker-03] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-08] You are going.
你正在离开。
[speaker-03] You're going to tell me what the access code is.
你会告诉我访问代码是什么吗？
[speaker-08] Oh, my God!
哦，天哪！
[speaker-08] Oh!
哦！
[speaker-06] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-08] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-01] Huh.
哼。
[speaker-08] Ugh!
啊！
[speaker-01] Ah!
[speaker-08] Wow.
哇。
[speaker-01] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-08] Get up.
起床。
[speaker-03] Ah!
啊！
[speaker-01] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-06] Roo!
好哇！
[speaker-06] Bah!
啊！
[speaker-08] Gag.
笑闹。
[speaker-01] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-01] Wow.
哇。
[speaker-08] Ah.
啊。
[speaker-01] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-08] Oh.
[speaker-01] Ah.
啊。
[speaker-08] Ugh.
呃。
[speaker-06] Ah.
啊。
[speaker-08] Ah!
啊！
[speaker-06] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-01] Oh.
[speaker-06] You, fuck!
你，该死！
[speaker-08] Come on, champ.
来吧，冠军。
[speaker-08] Good girl.
好女孩。
[speaker-01] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-01] Cut!
切！
[speaker-01] No.
不。
[speaker-06] Mother.
母亲。
[speaker-08] Wake up!
醒醒！
[speaker-03] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-01] Huh.
哼。
[speaker-08] Oh!
哦！
[speaker-08] Ah!
啊！
[speaker-06] Ugh.
呃。
[speaker-01] Ah.
啊。
[speaker-08] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-06] Oh.
[speaker-08] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-01] Oh.
[speaker-05] Get out of the way, Elton.
让开，埃尔顿。
[speaker-05] Stay down.
保持安静。
[speaker-06] He's not allowed to hurt me.
他不允许伤害我。
[speaker-03] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-07] Hmm.
嗯。
[speaker-06] Whoa.
哇。
[speaker-01] Ah.
啊。
[speaker-08] Yeah.
嗯。
[speaker-01] Ah.
啊。
[speaker-06] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-08] Yeah.
嗯。
[speaker-06] I'm sorry.
对不起。
[speaker-01] Ugh.
呃。
[speaker-06] No.
不。
[speaker-06] Whoa.
哇。
[speaker-06] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-06] Ah!
啊！
[speaker-06] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-08] Oh.
[speaker-01] Woah!
哇！
[speaker-08] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-01] Fuck you.
去你的。
[speaker-06] Go, Poppy.
去吧，波比。
[speaker-03] Fuck you, Poppy!
去你的，波比！
[speaker-03] Fuck you!
去你的！
[speaker-05] Elton.
埃尔顿。
[speaker-05] Kill Elton John.
杀死埃尔顿·约翰。
[speaker-08] Wow!
哇！
[speaker-01] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-08] Elton.
埃尔顿。
[speaker-03] Take the ball.
拿球。
[speaker-08] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-01] Oh.
[speaker-08] Go!
去吧！
[speaker-02] Thank you.
谢谢。
[speaker-02] Now.
现在。
[speaker-03] Go off and save the world.
去拯救世界吧。
[speaker-03] If I save the world.
如果我拯救了世界。
[speaker-02] Can I have two tickets to your next concert, darling?
亲爱的，我可以两张你下次的演唱会门票吗？
[speaker-03] save the world, you can have a backstage pass.
拯救世界，你可以获得后台入场券。
[speaker-01] Dah.
好的。
[speaker-06] Okay.
[speaker-08] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-06] Oh.
[speaker-08] Ugh.
呃。
[speaker-01] Time's up.
时间到。
[speaker-06] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-06] Huh.
哼。
[speaker-01] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-08] Beni.
本尼。
[speaker-05] Get them.
把它们拿过来。
[speaker-05] Go ahead.
请继续。
[speaker-03] Kill him.
杀了他。
[speaker-06] He's dead.
他已经死了。
[speaker-08] Heal, good boy!
康复了，好孩子！
[speaker-08] Come on!
快点！
[speaker-08] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-06] Give me the code.
给我代码。
[speaker-03] No, we're not done yet.
不，我们还没有完成。
[speaker-01] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-08] Ready, go.
准备好了，开始吧。
[speaker-01] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-08] Lucky for you.
幸运的是你。
[speaker-03] Charlie, one of us understands what it means to be a gentleman.
查理，我们中的一个人明白什么是绅士的行为准则。
[speaker-01] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-08] Huh?
嗯？
[speaker-01] Let's make this.
让我们来制作这个吧。
[speaker-03] Is this fair?
这公平吗？
[speaker-08] Ah!
啊！
[speaker-08] What?
什么？
[speaker-06] Ah, hello.
啊，你好。
[speaker-06] Ah!
啊！
[speaker-08] Wow.
哇。
[speaker-06] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-08] Ah.
啊。
[speaker-06] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-01] Ah!
啊！
[speaker-06] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-08] Oh.
[speaker-01] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-01] Ah.
啊。
[speaker-06] Come on!
来吧！
[speaker-06] Ah!
啊！
[speaker-08] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-06] Wow.
哇。
[speaker-08] Ah.
啊。
[speaker-01] Oh!
哦！
[speaker-08] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-03] Give me the code.
请提供代码。
[speaker-06] I can't.
我做不到。
[speaker-06] Only Buffy knows.
只有 Buffy 知道。
[speaker-03] Well, then you're not used to me, are you?
那么，你显然不习惯我，对吧？
[speaker-03] For the record, Charlie, I'm more of a gentleman than you'll ever be.
顺便说一下，查理，我更像是位绅士，你永远无法成为那样的人。
[speaker-03] But right now, it's time to drop the gentle bit.
但现在，是时候不再温柔了。
[speaker-03] This is for Kingsman.
这是为《王牌特工》准备的。
[speaker-03] For my mate, Brandon.
对于我的朋友 Brandon 来说。
[speaker-03] For Roxy.
对于 Roxy。
[speaker-03] For J.
对于 J.
[speaker-03] B.
[speaker-04] And for Merlin.
对于梅林也是如此。
[speaker-03] Good night, bruv.
晚安，兄弟。
[speaker-01] Hey.
嘿。
[speaker-05] Alice.
爱丽丝。
[speaker-02] You're going to give us the code.
你将给我们提供代码。
[speaker-06] Or what?
或者呢？
[speaker-05] 'Cause you don't seem like the kind of gentleman who would.
因为你看起来并不像会这么做的有礼人。
[speaker-05] Hurt a lady.
伤害了女士。
[speaker-02] Perhaps not.
也许不是。
[speaker-02] Got me old-fashioned.
我变得很老派了。
[speaker-02] I don't consider genocide, especially ladylike, right.
我不认为这是种族灭绝，尤其是那些关于女士的情节，对吧。
[speaker-03] Enough small talk.
足够的闲聊了。
[speaker-03] Give us the code.
请给我们代码。
[speaker-03] Sure.
当然。
[speaker-05] No, I don't think so.
不，我认为不是这样。
[speaker-06] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-06] No.
编号。
[speaker-03] Heroin.
海洛因。
[speaker-03] You know where I come from.
你知道我来自哪里。
[speaker-03] This shit you've been peddling ruined a lot of lives.
你贩卖的这东西毁了很多人的生活。
[speaker-03] The yours is even more deadly.
你的那种更致命。
[speaker-03] But it feels so nice.
但感觉真好。
[speaker-03] It's gonna make you lower your guard.
这会让你降低警惕。
[speaker-03] Our colleague.
我们的同事。
[speaker-02] Merlin.
梅林。
[speaker-02] May he rest in peace.
愿他安息。
[speaker-02] Managed to synthesize your horrible little formula and speed up its eff
成功合成了你那糟糕的配方，并加快了其效果
[speaker-02] So I would say you have just under eight minutes before paralysis sets i
所以我说，你还有不到八分钟时间，否则就会陷入瘫痪。
[speaker-02] n and your breathing stops.
你的呼吸停止了。
[speaker-02] But of course.
当然了。
[speaker-02] You know all about that.
你对此非常了解。
[speaker-02] So here's the deal.
所以，事情就是如此。
[speaker-03] You release the antidote worldwide, and we make sure you get a dose.
你在全球范围内释放解毒剂，我们会确保你能够获得足够的剂量。
[speaker-05] I have to give you the code to live, honey.
亲爱的，我得把生存代码给你。
[speaker-05] You're so smart.
你真聪明。
[speaker-05] You should work for me.
你应该为我工作。
[speaker-05] Give us the code.
请给我们代码。
[speaker-03] Here's the code.
这是代码。
[speaker-05] Why not?
为什么不行？
[speaker-05] The decree's getting.
法令正在制定中。
[speaker-05] Signed soon.
很快会发送。
[speaker-05] Anywho, um.
嗯，随便吧。
[speaker-05] Viva Las Vegan!
万岁纯素！
[speaker-05] Get it.
明白。
[speaker-06] Vegan.
纯素。
[speaker-05] Viva las.
万岁纯素！
[speaker-06] Hmm.
嗯。
[speaker-05] And come snuggle with me.
来和我依偎在一起吧。
[speaker-06] I like you.
我喜欢你。
[speaker-05] Thank you.
谢谢。
[speaker-02] I don't think that's terribly likely.
我认为这不太可能。
[speaker-06] Hmm.
嗯。
[speaker-01] I'm not a bad person.
我不是个坏人。
[speaker-02] She's Odeed.
她很开心。
[speaker-02] You gave her too much.
你给了她太多了。
[speaker-03] Did I?
是吗？
[speaker-03] I really don't have as much experience with all this drug stuff as peopl
我真的没有太多关于这种药物相关的经验。
[speaker-03] e think.
我认为。
[speaker-03] Better be the right code.
最好是正确的代码。
[speaker-01] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-02] V.
[speaker-06] Last.
最后。
[speaker-01] So.
所以。
[speaker-02] Don't move, kid.
别动，孩子。
[speaker-06] You try anything funny, and I'll turn.
你尝试任何有趣的方法，我就会转变。
[speaker-02] Not turn this thing electric.
不要让这东西变得有电一样。
[speaker-06] Now, give up your guns, fellas.
现在，伙计们，放下你们的枪吧。
[speaker-06] Slide 'em over.
把它们滑过去。
[speaker-03] Whisky, we are all on the same side here.
威士忌，我们都是同伙。
[speaker-03] You've had a head injury.
你受了头部受伤的伤。
[speaker-03] The exact same thing happened to Harry.
哈里也经历了完全相同的情况。
[speaker-03] You're having some sort of.
你们正在尝试某种有趣的方法。
[speaker-03] Brain glitch.
大脑故障。
[speaker-03] Nope.
不。
[speaker-06] My brain's all good, kid, and you know what?
我的大脑完全正常，孩子，你知道吗？
[speaker-06] I reckon the same was true for your friend Harry over here.
我认为你的朋友哈里也遇到了同样的情况。
[speaker-06] Real fine instincts.
很棒的直觉能力。
[speaker-06] I'll give him that.
我同意你的看法。
[speaker-06] So you stay still,
所以你保持不动吧，
[speaker-06] or I'll dice 'em up so small you can take 'em home in a bucket and still
或者我会把它们切得极小，你甚至可以用桶子带回家
[speaker-06] have room for what's left of your buddy Merlin.
还有空间容纳你朋友默林的残余部分。
[speaker-03] Well, that is just fucking great.
好吧，这真是太棒了。
[speaker-03] You're working for the president—that asshole.
你在为总统工作——那个混蛋。
[speaker-06] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-06] It's a matter of personal principle.
这是个人原则的问题。
[speaker-06] Agent, no more drug users.
代理，不再有吸毒者。
[speaker-06] And the statesmen share prize rockets.
那些政治家们也分享奖杯火箭。
[speaker-03] So, those are your principles.
所以，这些就是你的原则了。
[speaker-03] Making money.
赚钱。
[speaker-03] Our agencies were founded to uphold peace, to protect the innocent.
我们的机构成立是为了维护和平，保护无辜者。
[speaker-03] Do you want to know?
你想知道吗？
[speaker-06] Who was innocent?
谁是无辜的？
[speaker-06] My high school sweetheart.
我的高中恋人。
[speaker-06] Love of my life.
我生命中的挚爱。
[speaker-06] Pregnant with my little boy.
怀着我小儿子。
[speaker-06] He'd be about your age now.
他现在大概和你年龄相当。
[speaker-06] If his mama hadn't got caught in the crossfire when two methhead freaks
如果他妈妈没有在交火中被抓住，当时两个吸毒者正在打架
[speaker-06] decided to rob a fucking convenience store.
决定去抢劫一家该死的便利店。
[speaker-06] A world without those people in it.
一个没有那些人的世界。
[speaker-06] Sure, smells like peace to me.
当然，对我来说这闻起来像和平。
[speaker-06] You break the law.
你违反了法律。
[speaker-06] You pay the price.
你必须付出代价。
[speaker-06] Good riddance.
好极了，摆脱了。
[speaker-06] To all of them.
给他们所有人。
[speaker-01] I'm not a man.
我不是男人。
[speaker-06] That's why I got to destroy that case.
因此我不得不毁掉那个箱子。
[speaker-06] Now, slide it over, Agent Galahad.
现在，把它滑过去吧，加拉哈德Agent。
[speaker-01] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-06] Thank you.
谢谢。
[speaker-03] Do you know why, Harry?
你知道为什么吗，哈里？
[speaker-03] I think he's got a point.
我认为他说的有道理。
[speaker-03] I think it sounds like a bright idea.
我认为这听起来是个好主意。
[speaker-01] I'm not a bad person.
我不是个坏人。
[speaker-01] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-08] Whoa!
哇！
[speaker-08] Ugh!
[speaker-04] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-01] Ah.
啊。
[speaker-02] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-01] Oh.
[speaker-01] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-01] Ah.
啊。
[speaker-08] Oh my God!
哦，我的天！
[speaker-08] Ah!
啊！
[speaker-01] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-08] Oh, God.
哦，天哪。
[speaker-01] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-08] Put alpha gel.
放一点Alpha凝胶。
[speaker-03] What's your on that?
你那是什么？
[speaker-06] Dickhead.
蠢货。
[speaker-03] We were lost, vegan.
我们迷路了，是个纯素者。
[speaker-03] This one's for you, Merlin.
这是给你的，梅林。
[speaker-03] It's a day of worldwide celebration.
这是一场全球性的庆祝活动。
[speaker-04] as.
正如。
[speaker-06] As millions rejoice after they or their loved ones were saved from death
当数百万人在自己或所爱的人从死亡中获救后欢庆时
[speaker-01] Oh, do you want to?
哦，你愿意吗？
[speaker-05] I don't want to talk about it.
我不想谈论这件事。
[speaker-05] I'm scared.
我害怕。
[speaker-05] Distribution of the Golden Circle and.
金环组织的分布。
[speaker-06] Antidote continues.
解毒剂继续。
[speaker-05] and field hospitals are emptying as victims return to their homes tonigh
随着受害者们回到家中，那些野战医院正在逐渐空无。
[speaker-05] Cured.
已治愈。
[speaker-08] Thank you.
谢谢。
[speaker-01] I'm not afraid.
我不害怕。
[speaker-08] I'm not afraid to die.
我不害怕死亡。
[speaker-01] I'm going to get you.
我将带走你。
[speaker-08] We're going to win.
我们将会获胜。
[speaker-01] Yes.
是的。
[speaker-03] Yes.
[speaker-01] Yes, bro.
是的，兄弟。
[speaker-03] Yes!
太好了！
[speaker-03] Oh!
哦！
[speaker-08] I have.
我有。
[speaker-03] I love you, man.
我爱你，兄弟。
[speaker-03] I love you.
我爱你。
[speaker-03] I'm never touching that shit again.
我再也不会碰那东西了。
[speaker-01] What happened?
发生了什么？
[speaker-03] I need something.
我需要一些东西。
[speaker-05] We sure did.
我们当然确定。
[speaker-05] From now on, tequila.
从现在开始，龙舌兰酒。
[speaker-05] I suggest you stick to booze.
我建议你还是继续喝酒吧。
[speaker-05] The president actively sanctioned the deaths of hundreds of millions of
总统积极批准了数亿人的死亡事件
[speaker-05] people.
人。
[speaker-05] And lied to the public.
对公众撒了谎。
[speaker-05] I am proud to be responsible for his impeachment.
我很自豪能负责他的弹劾案。
[speaker-05] And I will do everything I can to ensure a smooth transition of power.
我将尽我所能确保权力平稳过渡。
[speaker-06] In honor of this historic occasion.
为了纪念这一历史性的时刻。
[speaker-06] We have purchased.
我们已经购买。
[speaker-06] A distillery in Scotland.
苏格兰的一家酿酒厂。
[speaker-03] Okay.
好的。
[speaker-01] This show.
这个节目。
[speaker-06] the world that Kingsmen is now.
“Kingsmen”现在的世界状况。
[speaker-06] Join the liquor business.
加入酒业领域。
[speaker-06] Before we were cousins.
在我们成为堂兄弟之前。
[speaker-06] Now we're brothers, working side by side.
现在我们是兄弟，一起并肩工作。
[speaker-06] All our resources are now yours.
所有资源现在都属于你。
[speaker-06] You can rebuild.
你可以重新构建。
[speaker-01] Yeah, y'all shitting.
是的，你们真厉害。
[speaker-04] And then hot cotton.
然后还有热棉花。
[speaker-06] Now.
现在。
[speaker-01] Agent De.
代理 De.
[speaker-06] DeKayla, this is a formal occasion.
DeKayla，这是一次正式场合。
[speaker-06] Where's your tie and jacket?
你的领带和夹克在哪儿？
[speaker-06] Sorry, sir.
抱歉，先生。
[speaker-01] Maybe the king.
也许是国王。
[speaker-06] boys can dress you properly.
男孩们能帮你穿得体。
[speaker-06] To our union.
致我们的联盟。
[speaker-02] This is the army.
这是军队。
[speaker-06] Final order of business.
最终事务顺序。
[speaker-06] We would be honored if one of you would be our new agent, whiskey.
如果您中的某位能成为我们的新代理人，我们将非常荣幸， whiskey。
[speaker-03] Yeah, this uh, two Galahad thing.
是的，这就是那个所谓的“加勒哈德”事情。
[speaker-06] is, just.
是，只是。
[speaker-03] fucking confusing.
太令人困惑了。
[speaker-06] Oh.
哦。
[speaker-02] Well.
嗯。
[speaker-03] I'm very honoured.
我非常荣幸。
[speaker-02] By the.
通过。
[speaker-05] Champ.
冠军。
[speaker-05] I'd like to throw my hat in the ring.
我想参与竞争。
[speaker-06] All right.
好的。
[speaker-06] Stake in the vote.
投票中的股份。
[speaker-06] Looks like she's in.
看起来她已经入场了。
[speaker-06] Have a seat.
请坐吧。
[speaker-01] Hm.
嗯。
[speaker-06] Dijon whiskey.
迪琼威士忌。
[speaker-03] Agent Whiskey.
代理威士忌。
[speaker-06] Cheers.
谢谢。
[speaker-02] Are you sure I don't look like a dick?
你确定我看起来不像混蛋吗？
[speaker-02] Look in the mirror.
看看镜子里的自己。
[speaker-02] What do you see?
你看到了什么？
[speaker-02] Someone who can't believe what the fuck is going on.
一个无法相信正在发生什么的人。
[speaker-01] I say, man.
我说，兄弟。
[speaker-02] A man who's honourable.
一个正直的人。
[speaker-02] Brave.
勇敢。
[speaker-02] Loyal.
忠诚。
[speaker-02] Who's fulfilled his huge potential.
谁已经发挥了他的巨大潜力。
[speaker-02] A man who's done something good with his life.
一个已经用自己的一生做了些有意义事情的人。
[speaker-03] I owe you everything, Harry.
我欠你一切，哈里。
[speaker-03] Thank you.
谢谢。
[speaker-02] Don't mention it.
不客气。
[speaker-02] You ready?
你准备好了吗？
[speaker-03] Not a doubt in my mind.
我心中没有疑问。
[speaker-01] I'm not sure what I'm doing.
我不确定自己在做什么。
[speaker-07] I'm not afraid to die.
我不怕死。
[speaker-08] I'm not afraid to die.
[speaker-02] As one of our founding kingsmen once said.
正如我们的创始领袖之一所说。
[speaker-02] This is not the end.
这还不是结束。
[speaker-02] It is not even the beginning of the end.
这甚至还不是结束的开始。
[speaker-02] But it is perhaps.
但也许是这样吧。
[speaker-02] The end of the beginning.
终结的开始。
[speaker-01] I'm not a man.
我不是男人。
[speaker-08] I'm not a hero.
我不是英雄。
[speaker-05] I'm not sure.
我不确定。
[speaker-08] You know.
你知道的。
[speaker-01] I'm not a man.
我不是男人。
[speaker-08] I'm not a man.
[speaker-08] I'm not afraid to die.
我不怕死。
[speaker-08] I'm not a hero.
我不是英雄。